#1178: But duplicate loses

Along with the passage of Cooldown, HP of seizing were also getting fewer and fewer, when BOSS HP falls to below 10%, my heartbeat speed was also getting more and more fast, but the distant place, the clear pupil develops on the face of black ink to have the smiling face of pondering as before, reason that calmly certainly was confident, what was her card in a hand?

In this time, suddenly behind crowd „” has promoted several pitch-dark „crossbow car(riage)”, is pushed to transport by one group of players.

It is not right!

That is not the crossbow car(riage), in shooting trough, what is placing obviously is decorating the big net of iron awl, moreover is the network of wire rope knitting, reflects very honest color under the sunlight, looks at this situation, I instantaneous such as the falling ice hole, some back rounds were cold, the clear pupil develops black ink to have this being used capture big dragon, warhawk and other flight species unexpectedly hunting for Long Nu, but this these hunt for Long Nu to prepare to my this Dragon Rider gentleman!

The whole person thought instantaneously was not quite good, had a look at seizing in ground, the blood strip to brush to fall again, leaves my Cooldown to be getting fewer and fewer, if necessary must open the invincible skill to clash really!

„7%!”

„6%!”

„5%!”

Almost every second of BOSS blood strip fiercely is reducing, Cooldown are not many, when achieves 3% HP, means for 10 seconds BOSS to die, this was my opportunity!

Sets firm resolve, dies dies, overruns to snatch!

„Brushes!”

Thousand frost wings, dived directly, the double sword flew high, rumbles [Seven Star Fragment Slash], the sword air/Qi punctures thoroughly the back of BOSS, fell in the front crowd, blew out to strike fatally, the instantaneous second killed 78 people, simultaneously my body also close ground 50 yards.

„Is now!”

In the ground, transmits the clear pupil to develop the squeal of black ink, not far away, hunt for Long Nu in abundance the adjustment direction, the next quarter the iron networks of super revolving projects on „brushes”, I look clearly, the body in the airborne anxious spin, continuously twice changes, MISS fell four clathrias, simultaneously the body tenesmuss suddenly, comes again, [Combo] [Wind Blade] falls after BOSS carries on the back, the whole person also almost rode after BOSS carried on the back.

„”

Miserable howling, seizing Tarhun is roaring falling to the ground, although I am destroying, but attack of one group of Indian players has not actually stopped, the result that in fact they want blows out the Holy Ghost treasure box, they do not care as for equipment that this five-star god level BOSS blows out, the five-star magical instrument is unable to place on a par with the influence that the Holy Ghost treasure box brings, and duty that this is the Indian war zone is in the seven luminaries city territory that presents, if had been snatched by others, that negative impact too was big.

„On!”

Surroundings, one crowd of Berserker, swordsmen and knight flushed in abundance, flies high among equipment and sundry goods that falls, a shining valuable box also, Holy Ghost treasure box!

In my heart the great happiness, the [Seven Stars Teleportation] position fell, a twinkle arrived at a day of authority, fights the boots to tread blows out the [Ice Domain] effect, surrounding one group of people majority of frozen, put out a hand to hold the Holy Ghost treasure box, admitted the package, jumped to fly, should walk!

„Bites!”

System announcement: Players 【Xiao Yao Zi Zai】( China) obtained the Holy Ghost treasure box, the position that he is in seven luminaries forest ( 31177,24991 ), kills this player 100% to blow out the Holy Ghost treasure box, gained the Holy Ghost treasure box to maintain for 7 hours to obtain the treasure in Holy Ghost treasure box!

In the team channel has broadcast the Lin Wan Er sound: „Ha, is quite fierce, snatched really!”

Dong Cheng Yue: „Worthily is our eldest children, hee hee!”

But, in two female praise sounds, I actually slightly also happy, when because I fly to 10 meters altitude, is not already able to fly was higher, Holy Ghost treasure box had to limit my flight altitude, otherwise I flew into ten thousand meters upper air directly, that feared others naturally unable how me.

„Hunts for Long Nu, hurry up!” The vice- Guildmaster iron boots of beautiful life concentrate black ink to shout loudly.

Meanwhile, the clear pupil develops black ink to hit one side the player who calibrates hunts for Long Nu suddenly, calibrates personally, in a pair of beautiful pupil is passing the spunk.

My angle was almost blocked completely, in the ground the innumerable bow arrow, magic and sword air/Qi raids, simultaneously „brushes” consecutively three to hunt for Longwang to fly, I halt forcefully, this evading will, without enough time rejoiced that suddenly one cold, the ice wing that raspberry transforms was unable to open, was wrapped all round by a big net.

Bad!

Almost is less than one second, is three iron nets twines me at the different angles, letting the human is unable to fly also considers as finished but actually, what awfully is the iron net is too heavy, leading me not to be self-possessed crashes!

Awfully, HP less than 20%, words not [Drain] that did not kill people, could not shoulder!

Not the body of extinguishing!

Roars, the body of extinguishing already did not open, but I also instantaneously fall to the ground at the same time, one group of knights were the player progress, iron shield „bang bang bang” the hit in the surroundings, somewhat was simply cruel, [Tempest Sword] started, simultaneously above the sword blade edge Lei Guang pasted, summoned [Thundering Heavens] directly, erupted sturdy thunder and lightning bombing centered on me, Thunder dragon wreaked havoc, the surrounding player instantaneously was also massacred one piece.

However, I am unable to fly as before, surrounding protecting shield „flip-flop” by the opposite party long-distance is outputting violently, even the clear pupil developed black ink to draw the arrow to kill me, even if I drank next health potion, but the effect of body of extinguishing did not vanish my second will kill instantaneously, such may anything end!

„Raspberry!” I shout loudly: „Opens the net!”

Hides in the raspberry prompt response in my within the body, the ice wing elongates the energy to transform together is the dragon claw, is accompanying raspberry faintly drinks the sound tenderly, „” one side wire rope net ripping open, at the same time, my double sword round screw has divided to cut forward, two handle swords both are the five-star magical instruments, is sharp, „” iron net tearing into shreds.

Good, was free!

However, has not waited for me to be happy, the rear area is one „whiz” sound, is a standing net after binds me, the iron online is also bringing the thorn, punctures incomparable the ache on the skin.

„Surrounds him, do not let him clash, does not hesitate the price!” The clear pupil develops black ink to shout in the rear area loudly.

She does not know body of extinguishing persistent Cooldown.

Then, I drag a big net to clash forward, enemy who execution of sword sword blocks the way, however the speed could not raise, it is well known the acceleration of mount has an increasing speed process, the increasing speed process of raspberry is about 1-3 seconds, however by the great net limiting, this speed definitely is unable to raise.

The clear pupil develops black ink and iron boots to congeal black ink and the others to dread my kills the ability only, does not approach, but even if I move with the [Seven Stars Teleportation] position am also bringing the great net, is in surrounding of one group of Indian players, walks radically does not escape.

A huge choice arrives before me, here waits to be killed, gives up the Holy Ghost treasure box, first maintains life?

Words that puts together hardly, overlord coverall can indeed let my rebirth and promotes 30% entire attributes, however periphery is others people, I at least must die 4-5 times to guarantee that makes them completely not broken guards, that price not necessarily was also too big, and does not know that the death of overlord rebirth, can blow out the Holy Ghost treasure box, once were robbed, same has wasted the golden opportunity.

The rapid decision, can enter to draw back, the side is the best plan!

In the instance that the body of extinguishing does not vanish, I pull out the Holy Ghost treasure box to get rid from the package in the ground, immediately the body is relaxed, as if has untied an ancient seal, a double sword round dance, cuts the wire rope, rises straight from the ground, this nobody can block me, since the whole person almost 1 second flew 30 meters, the clear pupil developed black ink aiming unable to follow my flying speed.

„, Is about she to stand in the ground really”, surprised visits me, said: „Iron boots, you take the Holy Ghost treasure box!”

In the system announcement, is demonstrating one „player 【Xiao Yao Zi Zai】( China) has discarded the Holy Ghost treasure box”, thinks that the player of entire server also knows I have not gone well.

„What happened, are pig you all right?” Concern of Lin Wan Er in the forming a team channel asked.

I flies the blood, while said: „All right, but the Holy Ghost treasure box was really too hot, the clear pupil developed black ink not to my this opportunity, Wan Er you were also careful, the prudent attack, the clear pupil developed inside black ink to have the type of crossbow car(riage) to be called ‚hunts for dragon crossbow’, to the airborne unit having strong limit ability, I was because this hunted for Long Nucai to suffer a loss . Moreover, had the person of Holy Ghost treasure box unable to fly to exceed 10 meters, therefore the Dragon Rider gentleman did not have what superiority.”

Lin Wan Er „not”: „Good, I planned to change, is really the difficult office.”

Dong Cheng Yue said: „We now what to do?”

I: „I will fly in the upper air, with the Holy Ghost treasure box, once there is an opportunity again to get rid, I do not believe the clear pupil to develop black ink to push am hunting for Long Nu to walk everywhere.”

„That” Lin Wan Er somewhat worried that said: „If they take the Holy Ghost treasure box to enter the seven luminaries city, we did want the storm their main city? Several ten million people defend a city, we did not have any opportunity.”

I nod: „Yes, I was also worrying that this issue, was too thorny, how long Li Mu can they also?”

„Two after at least hours.”

„Is a little slow”

„Um, waits again, certainly will have the new opportunity.”

„Um!”

At this moment, I gain ground, in the jungle of distant place presented nattierblues, and with serious hoofbeat, immediately my moral nature one happy, in the top of the head of this group of people brought the stars and stripes, the person in US war zone to come finally!

The strong gale rides, war sharp knife blade Guild strongest branch of the services, is the biggest card in a hand of sky rose!

South the jungle, tens of thousands of strong gales rode already the player who started to cover kills the beautiful life, the speed of sky rose really ultra-fast, I not long she had the human to arrive to here.

Has the person of Holy Ghost treasure box is the iron boots concentrates black ink, he is holding the valuable box, while shouts loudly: „Clear pupil, we now what to do? The cavalry regiment of impact sky rose, turns head to seek for other direction?”

The clear pupil develops black ink to gain ground looks from afar to me in upper air, in the beautiful pupil is passing reluctantly: „It is not good, Xiao Yao that soul is defending pale still, once we disperse are not easy to do, frontage [Assault], fights a decisive battle with war sharp knife blade Guild, so long as breaks through their offensive, we can enter the seven luminaries city, when the time comes no one want to bribe the Holy Ghost treasure box!”

„Good!”

#1206: Goes down to the tiger's den

„Brushes!”

Breaks through „diaphragm”, I raised the two handle god bright sharp knife blade to enter the base of storm abyss, at present lets the flame and storm that the human is unable to endure vanishes instantaneously does not see, displacing truly together the light beam that projected from the heaven falls into the boundless darkness, I looked up, only saw that fierce big eye was stirring the storm and flame, made me realize that this big eye was the energy storage of storm abyss, because it formed such one to be similar to the terrain of energy funnel.

Flew following the light beam, flew approximately for nearly 10 minutes, the skylight discarding above a main hall, that is the main hall that the blue stone brick paves, simple, but **, the main hall surroundings are standing sword Armor bright military, looks are dignified, if not corners of the mouth corruption slightly, I even think that these people are not the dead souls, but is the live person.

But I drop from the clouds, the wings opens, suddenly the feelings of some heaven being near angels, naturally, I to do not think attentively weakly really one are the angel, I am a player, comes to here is to seek to wear.

As if has not noted me in space, in the ground one group of military are practicing diligently.

Grasps the old man of walking stick, the beard and hair is all white, the one side of trembling arriving main hall, said with the old sound: „This is the fourth selection, becomes the demon palace guards looked today's has fought, Zhao Jin, you to fighting Xu Yan, who can win, who can obtain side the great honor that wearing your highness holds the post to guard!”

Two military walked, grasps the long sword to bow, said: „Yes, elder!”

Xu Yan?

My whole body trembles, wasn't this crazy Lei Jun's once commanding? Is the country is utterly loyal in Fan Shu City died in battle, how to appear here? Looks at the appearance, truly is Xu Yan, was he resurrected into the dead souls soldier?

It seems like truly was this, Xu Yan once was also the department audiences who wore, now is competing to wear the great honor of near body guard with another dead?

Moral nature even more heavy, who this is, if the real Tian Ling Empire little princess wears, why she does not go to Tian Ling Empire to look for me, why will mobilize the army to slaughter the Tian Ling Empire player? Certainly is not, this person possibly is not wears.

In the field, Xu Yan and Zhao Jin two people have fought with all might in the same place, the feat of arms collision burst out the roaring flame and incorruptible, the entire main hall slightly is also shivering because of the fights of these two people, I fix the eyes on to look, Xu Yan feat of arms as if compares living time nearly strove? Carefully looked that discovered that Xu Yan is two star god general officer levels BOSS, but Zhao Jin will be a star god, this no wonder, but after Xu Yan died in battle, unexpectedly the strength will not fall instead rises, this many will make people somewhat be hard to approve.

After several rounds, a Xu Yan advance cuts to strike, immediately that Zhao Jin drops down slowly, the nape of the neck place presented a bloodstain, the body collapses to disperse into pile of rotten hashed meat suddenly, Xu Yan sneers, the bending down body is gnawing the flesh and blood of match, buys to change into oneself to use his part of strengths.

„Xu Yansheng!”

The elder is raising staff , to continue to say with the old sound: „Zhao Jin Jingzhong duty, died, he is an honourable person, what a pity, he did not have the qualifications to become guarding of your highness! Continue, met to meet Wang Chao by Qin Xiong, a person that in you determined the final outcome may also become demon palace guard who wore your highness!”

Another two BOSS level military also fight with all might in the same place, I understood finally, here is one compared with the practice grounds, moreover is a god level compared with the practice grounds, in this main hall is standing all people are star-level BOSS, fearful, in the purgatory like this selects the talented person? Must know that BOSS of god general officer level is rare in Tian Ling Empire, entire palace guard not over 5 people, but in this small main hall has over 20 god level BOSS unexpectedly, was too fearful!

„Clang!”

Qin Xiong Axe flood Lei Guang, was shining the surrounding all, under one of the match time selected to cut ingeniously, his Axe by the Georgian parry came, to let go to fly!

„Brushes!”

Brings Lei Guang Axe to dash to me, but I am hurried am sideways to evade, but dozens god level BOSS in ground saw me, Xu Yangeng is one recognizes me, loudly shouted to clear the way: „Is commanding Li Xiao Yao of Tian Ling Empire palace guard, will he arrive in the purgatory? On, kills him together, takes his head to take undeserved credit to your highness!”

Xu Yan jumps, the long sword belt the flame is dividing to me.

Once defeated, I naturally cannot pay attention, let alone he is only two star gods!

Occupies a commanding position, under my double sword raises to press together, „bang” flame spatters in all directions, under the heavy pressure must back up directly the hit Xu Yanhong above the main hall, the blue stone was shattered, this demon palace guards is really also distressed enough, but several other god level BOSS also flushed, I cannot a person select that many people only , can only in the riches and honor danger ask, dives directly, directly soars that elder, captures the ringleader first!

„Buzz!”

The Zheng of butterfly with doing above will be calling the sword air/Qi sound, started 7 times to cut to strike instantaneously swiftly and fiercely, performs to scold above staff of this elder, but the elder is the five-star god, but as if did not plan that with appearance that I battled, raised staff with the aid of instead to shake the strength to draw back dozens meters continually, shouted to clear the way lowly: „Li Xiao Yao, what do you come to storm purgatory to make?”

I am built on same place, ice wing fan slightly, said: „Leads me to see to wear.”

„Sees your highness?”

Long on shameless passed over gently and swiftly heterochrosis, said with a smile: „You want to see to wear your highness, for what?”

„Because she is my old friend.”

„, Right?” The elders show a faint smile, lift the hand saying: „Audiences, will stop attacking, this person must see to wear your highness, since this, that obsolete led him to see your highness to be good, you continued to stay here to select the demon palace guard, Xu Yan, Wang Chao, you were selected in the demon palace guard, with me together, sending under custody Li Xiao Yao to go to the demon palace to see your highness.”

„Yes!” Two two star god level BOSS respectful holds the fist in the other hand to acknowledge.

In this purgatory was too dark, I then lift the arm, holds up the butterfly high, the ray of five-star magical instrument shines a about 10 meters range, lets me to obtain some precious fields of vision.

Nearby the corridor along main hall walked for nearly 10 minutes, proceeding is black sea, I cannot bear say: „What is this?”

„The sea of death.” The elder corners of the mouth raise, say with a smile: „Holds the spear not to come the ghostdom greatly, thinks that hasn't seen this sea? Careful, do not fall down, even if otherwise had the exceedingly high skill to be also beyond redemption!”

I frown to have a look, indeed, including the sea water is the black, turns in mighty waves that wells up face of faintly visible calling out, looked like the ghost that sought for the scapegoat is the same, falls down perhaps really died, but I, since came not to fear death but actually, so long as can see to wear, basically my duty has been accomplished, now what I most want to know, this was Tian Ling Empire?

The elders lift staff, the acme of barrier in the nighttime sky flood the blue ray, simultaneously he also loudly shouts: „One-eyed, ferries quickly, the guest came!”

The distant place, a pale yellow small lamp was slowly near, was one swings the person of small boat to come, really be only an eye, a fierce eye, the rickets the body was bending down in the stern, the elder embarked immediately, I also stepped the deck, simultaneously gained ground to have a look at the sky, as if shadows from the sky passed over gently and swiftly, what was that?

„Do not look.” The elders ponder visits me, said with a smile: „Holds Ge Ke not to try to enter the sky greatly, otherwise your fate beyond redemption will be more miserable.”

I: „”

Unexpectedly had been threatened by NPC, this taste does not feel better, but this had the suggestion of threat expression I to accept with pleasure, stubborn of not needing donkey temperament, in this place, the smart person can live for a long time.

The small boat dragged slowly in the sea of death, this ferry nearly 20 minutes, the distant place has transmitted the dim light finally, shortly after proceeded again, finally was brilliantly illuminated, the innumerable lanterns were hanging by the path, the front was a quite palatial palace, was almost equally matched with the Tian Ling Empire imperial palace, but the guards were some deads, and distant can see that some lighting the lamps corpse ghosts were in the garden You Yi, these lighting the lamps corpse ghosts to the player was the symbol of death, but to Hybrid Demon, the lighting the lamps corpse ghost probably with delivering express similar, ignored.

„Holds the spear greatly, don't you want to see your highness? Comes with me!” The elders show a faint smile.

I disembark with him slowly, proceeds following the track, corpse ghost who the both sides fiercely roar, the step of elder is slow, I do not worry, step by step.

Walked for several minutes, finally entered this palace.

Is being ready in full battle array demon palace rides all the way everywhere, just here demon palace rides no longer is 7 levels of Hybrid Demon, but was promoted 8 levels of Hybrid Demon, the attribute violent increased much, the skill also strengthened, these wear the branch of the services that trained in the purgatory? Wears before death is a girl of being competent, after dying, has such achievement as before, as if I early should think.

One crowd of Pandemonium ride to me glower, as if momentarily planned that rips the smashing me.

Endured with great difficulty entered the road in main hall, the stair of first-level level went nonstop to hundred meters high main hall, when I stepped the main hall unexpectedly has had an illusion, was here the Tian Ling Empire imperial palace?

Obviously some superficial elephants, but real actually missed were too many, was built on by the main hall was not the civil and military hundred officers, dead but who whole bodies covered entirely the livor mortis, but has swept one, I was secret the heart startled, in this small main hall, 12 five-star god level BOSS , 30 + four star god level BOSS, let out completely can definitely cause the worldwide chaos!

And, highest is also not five-star god level BOSS, two king level BOSS!

On the throne of command, an exquisite fine form sits there, is throwing over the blood red cape, a handle long sword slanting by near her leg . Moreover, the front of this woman is embroidering a very striking golden mark, that is the Tian Ling Empire symbol!

#1207: Thousand strange

Is this person wears really? She has with wearing the common figure, has all makings of wearing, and accessories of clothes with wearing exactly the same, do I also hold true by thinking this woman am not wear?

But if, she wears , can also sitting safely here?

Even if at heart 10,000 question marks, but I have stood here, the glory can not I go to think much.

Commands the one side of throne, the Hybrid Demon king who wears the flame mail-armor and helmet stands there, the hand is grasping a handle golden color long sword, Hybrid Demon king [Judgement] who is listed 7 th!

In body of [Judgement] not livor mortis, does not have what corrupt sign, BOSS of genuine king level does not have slight defect that their statures tended to be perfect, this [Judgement] about 30 -year-old high and low appearance, an imposing healthy tendency of face, naturally, this should be the false appearance, a face imposing person will not stand there.

„Hey, boy!”

[Judgement] looks to me, lets somebody cool off or calm down says with a smile: „Were you scared? Sees to wear your highness, why ritual of not the good worshipping on bended knees?”

I use the equally ice-cold sound saying: „I know that this person is not wears!”

„Right?”

Sat woman on command throne lifts the hand to lift the cape, immediately a beautiful cheek appears in me at present, the voice and face smiling face, in the woman who in my mind cannot circle, who wasn't wears can be?

„You” my words choke up all of a sudden in the throat, does not know that said anything was good.

Wears visits me with a smile: „Li Xiao Yao, you said actually that I am not wear, who am I?”

Standing that I had nothing to say in reply there.

In wears stands up, shakes hand the pointed weapons, lets somebody cool off or calm down says with a smile: „Good deed that Li Xiao Yao, you do, I entrust the palace guard and empire to you, making you assist two emperor brother government day plume empires well, finally you have made anything, your illicit intercourse Seurre has killed my two emperor brothers unexpectedly, then brought in the northern barbarian to enter Tian Ling Empire, what was more hateful was you assists that barbarian's son shallow Rinden to get up the throne unexpectedly!”

In her eye gushes out boundless angry and disappointment, said: „Li Xiao Yao, you disappointed me, I am these that wanted you to do? Tian Ling Empire had been ruined by your one, the bloodlines of imperial family already no longer pure, but your this despicable power secretly for win the throne of empire marshal, made that many to be unfair to my matter, you told me, the throne of this empire marshal, did you sit do not think such as the point in the back?”

I stand there silently, was worn a series of words to ask feels like a knife twisting in the heart, yes, I do what is?

[Judgement] Jie Jie laughs, seemed ridiculing my distress.

Several seconds later, suddenly I gained ground, an eye becomes limpid, looks at present, said: „All that I made in the past think to have a clear conscience, dies in his clinging to authority, succeeding to the throne of shallow forest can let the empire long-term peace and good government, can cut off truly to watch for the idea of imperial throne, the internal disorder and foreign invasion, I have defended the day of plume empire with a conscience, and turned into three from one empire main city, I have a clear conscience, but you, are not wear radically!”

Wears stares, corners of the mouth reappearing smiling face: „I am not wear, who is?”

I smile lightly: „Wears passes on my Saint day jue, wants me to give priority to the world, how such woman will support the soldier to be self-possessed in the purgatory, how to take sacrificing the life chooses the demon palace guard as the price, how also to train that many Hybrid Demon armies to threaten the safety in seven big kingdoms, you are not wear, you do not match her name!”

Wears stands up suddenly, in the eye full is the spunk, shouted to clear the way lowly: „Li Xiao Yao, what thing you are, do you dare to question me? Told you, you come here not to live today, I will make you die here!”

Saying, her was jumping suddenly , the left hand area pulled out the family background side sharp sword, personal appearance such as electricity arrived in front of me, before I resisted turned around to strike, the sword blade edge chopped in my front, carried over thousand + the injury digit, the good pain, this was only the injury of ordinary attack!

Is suppressing the ache, I prick in the butterfly sword her arms rapidly, turned the hand a buckle, the sword hilt covered her sword hilt, simultaneously did the sword makes an effort to strike, almost notch completely my full strength hit forward, „bang” will wear hits left same place, layer on layer hit with me together on nearby stone column, the dust rustle sprinkled, the entire palace also position slightly trembled, I looked straight ahead her look, the anger am exclaiming: „Who you are, which did you wearing get so far as? You are not wear, you at all are not wear!”

In her eye is bringing light teasing, said: „No, I am wear, hee hee, besides me, but also who can be wears? You come, feels my breath, feels my hug, feels my human body, you will discover that I am wear, my whole body does not have one is not wears, but”

She presses aggressively in my front, suddenly put out a hand to refer to own chest, the demon said: „Just here is not wears, this heart, is my, ha”

On my shoulder transmits the fierce ache, is the attack of [Judgement], fell 200 000 + HP.

Wears continues to visit me, the pretty face becomes fierce, Ha Ha said with a smile: „You asked that which I got so far as your went, I can tell you now, I have swallowed her, Ha Ha, the old lady has swallowed this small **, what no matter I she were what empire princess, I only know that this leather bag let me to attract the talented people in many ghosts to be adopted by us, come, Li Xiao Yao, you were the snow and ice goddess Frost disciple, weren't you very strong? Cuts open my chest, casts off this heart, you can drive away the body of wearing me, do you want your? Ha Ha, has killed me, making you obtain princess of a having no interest, how is it?”

Is facing her crazed, I will erupt [Strength of a Thousand Men] combo suddenly, the bracing cold will wear to shake rapidly, simultaneously will mobilize the abdomen that will ride the wind to cut the bang in wearing, will blow out a series of injuries at the same time, carried on the back and encounters has struck, the order [Judgement] attack of [Judgement] was too strong, in an instant polished my HP, player could a flesh and blood, how possibly withstand the collaboration attacks of two demon god level Hybrid Demon kings?

Sobs, at present one bright, hung.

However has chosen in same place rebirth, under the overlord rebirth effect promoted 30% entire attributes, the defensive power also violent to increase much, turned round is [Tempest Sword] + 3 times attacks the bang to draw back [Judgement].

Transmits the tepid feeling, wears opens the snow white arm to grasp me unexpectedly, the steam was saying with a smile near my ear: „Li Xiao Yao, don't you want to feel to wear princess's body? She is a princess, doesn't the princess of descendant of the imperial family, you want to hold? Come, I in you, so long as you take an oath to give loyalty to me, I make you hold me.”

I am angry, the both arms shake to hit her suddenly, is sideways is an attractive side kicks, tramples her continually to draw back several steps, gets angry: „The body that shame like this do not wear, your this despicable devil, tumbled out the body that wore!”

She actually and does not care, stands up slowly, raises the long sword to say with a smile: „What's wrong, do you that treasure her body? Ha, Li Xiao Yao, will your this ordinary people understand that type joyfully? You do not want me not to relate, have this perfect body, I can recruit more god level powerhouse, I can wait upon in their crotches persuasively, I can make them enjoy my each inch flesh, this body for me is only a human body, what kind, vitality? Come, massacres me, does not massacre me, I make [Judgement] enjoy this body tonight, making him fully enjoy to be overwhelmed with emotion the taste of eclipse bone!”

[Judgement] is raising the golden long sword, said with a smile lightly: „Wears, did your agree make me probably recompense finally to look?”

Wears sneers: „Premise is, you can massacre this Tian Ling Empire held the spear to say greatly again! So long as removes this person, Tian Ling Empire numerous regiments command definitely meet the internal strife to be unceasing, when the time comes our cavalry soldiers trample flat Tian Ling Empire simply are easy as pie, on, massacres Li Xiao Yao with me together, making his soul forever stay in the storm purgatory!”

Looks to wear, my aggrieved in the extreme, the tears almost fell, this time, what I can make, what can I achieve to protect once that empire princess?

About hundred star-level BOSS flushed together, various skill connection, even if my resistance has promoted 30%, but HP rapidly falls, stuffy snort fell once more first-level, choice same place resurrecting, I do not dare dead in battle as before, if dies here, the overlord coverall will be very likely to fall one, the uneven words, my many efforts were in vain!

Must clash, here can only die!

Has promoted 60% attributes, the flying speed also violent increased, I turned around am a [Tempest Sword] anxious spin bang kill, twist to break to pieces the war armor of many Hybrid Demon commander, escaped, but [Judgement] and wore the keenly blowing to kill, they killed me to feel at ease assuredly.

On the face of [Judgement] full is just, Ha Ha said with a smile: „Empire holds the spear greatly, do not walk, accepts just [Judgement]!”

I am burning with anger, this so-called just [Judgement], after [Judgement] ends me, again in the body that on the bed „[Judgement]” does wear?

„Bang!”

The [Ice Domain] effect frozen was occupied by many people, I already ran out of the main hall, although behind also with dozens people, but flushed as before, goes to the ferry to go back?

Not was too possible, that one-eyed person certainly will not ferry first me, next, the ferry is too slow, may be killed on the ship. That can only fly from the space, is this airborne giant shadow, what are these?

Steels one's heart, shoots up to the sky, flies!

No matter these are anything, spells to try also to fly!

„Whish!”

Ices the wing outbreak, the whole person changed into ices the color advantage arrow to fire into the sky together.

„Jie Jie”

Airborne hears the crying out strangely sound, my rashly raises the sword directly is [Tempest Sword], the flame of airborne eruption makes me see the present all, that was one has the monsters of innumerable tentacle, did not have the face, only then filled the big mouth of innumerable advantage tooth, looked like extremely fearsome, 9 levels of Hybrid Demon, thousand strange!

#1209: Super excavator

„Massacres him, must massacre him, cannot put him to walk!”

Wore is almost insane outside was yelling, [Judgement] raised the long sword also to enter the rock cave, but this rock cave was really too small and narrow, even soon could not contain the [Judgement] spacious armor, his both hands were grasping the long sword, passed through my both feet and both legs with the long sword directly, an intermittent scalding hot injury transmitted, but has promoted 150% in my defensive power and HP well, did not fear that very much attack of [Judgement], his every struck can only create the thousand high and low attack to me, but my time [Cleansing Rain] technique on can restore thousand + HP, 7. seconds a [Cleansing Rain] technique, occasionally turns around to give him in addition a sword, such one in addition drinks the blood effects and 10% triggering Dinghai 50% HP restores the effect, almost can lossless select [Judgement] only!

However, my wish naturally is not this, but a bit faster hits thoroughly this day dome, does not leave here to face thousand strange threats finally, thousand strange thunder stroke techniques are the magic attack types, has the natural superiority to me, cannot carry on the shoulder hardly.

„Bang bang bang”

The crushed stone falls unceasingly, these form zenith the rock to be hard, the density is also much higher, pounds is very painful on the face, but I unceasing advance forward, holds the post of the heavy responsibility of mining coal to come as before, how whatever [Judgement] attacks, I as before am maintaining every minute at least 2 meters thorough progress, but this process also really extremely in the pain, wore also entered the rock cave along with [Judgement], and every several other seconds gave me to come a purple thunder bombardment, what awfully were, outside transmitted fiercely „flip-flop” sound, wore also orders thousand hands to unearth the zenith dome strangely together., Thousand strange statures are huge, look like excavators are the same, over ten thousand first thousand strange unearth the zenith together, had the blue flying in circles professional school former years the excavator specialized fellow apprentices together to return to the school to start greatly to unearth the imposing manner of joyful reunion.

It is not good, my speed must over thousand strange, fate that otherwise cannot escape from infinitely killed, even if I can massacre [Judgement] , but for a king falls dozens levels of this price too to be also big, I am the [Zhan Long] soul leader, once my Level falls that many, to the adverse impact that [Zhan Long] brings is also extremely serious.

Therefore, such crazily unearthed, did the sword 100% durably quick has consumed 60%, but the butterfly has never attrition effect, as before 100% durable.

Has unearthed fully for nearly 1 hour, I at least have dug out over 200 meters gulf, even soon could not hear thousand strange excavation sounds, did I throw off them?

Obviously, [Judgement] and wear also with me, thousand strange were throw off.

In this time, is wielding a sword chops to chop to transmit „biting” suddenly, the long sword chops to cut in silver iron ore, one cuts at least half meter depth, the rock was not hard, I have broken the zenith dome!

„Drop!”

System System Notification: You entered the map 【Storm abyss】!

Really, I left the storm purgatory, broke the purgatory with every knot, originally tied broke by the excavation technology, this was completely big my to be unexpected!

The [Judgement] fierce voice of conveys: „Does boy, which you want to run away to goes?”

I have a look at him, his blood strip fell 71%, is I links the merit that the disappearing belt hits, therefore upward unearths, while started to deal with [Judgement] with single-hearted devotion, since arrived every, that this Hybrid Demon king do not want to walk!

Opens the map system, 3 D surveys, I from surface about 7000 meters remote, um, that before entering the surface solves [Judgement], to Huppe, has if possible captures alive her, brings her Huilong territory, Frost will certainly have the means that naturally, this plan difficulty is too big, is very difficult to implement, in any event, massacres [Judgement] first is always right.

Turns round is one time rides the wind to cut, chops [Judgement] to be torn to pieces, my this time striking power was too high, rides the wind to cut the consecutively 15 swords, in addition murders the god and destiny card sign the damage that the strong single body attack effect, each sword causes certainly has surpassed thousand, this set rode the wind the complete attack output that cut already to cross thousand, king BOSS HP were most also on 10 E, how many complete sets can he withstand riding the wind of my to cut?

[Judgement] as if also felt strength perhaps bad, on the face passed over gently and swiftly startled, said: „Wears your highness, this boy as if obtained any supernatural power to be common, unexpectedly the strength multiplied, end end possibly is not his match!”

Wears is narrowing the eye: „Does not need to be worried that I in you behind, I expand this road immediately, with you by two enemies one, this boy must die today here!”

„Yes!”

Really, does not leave for several seconds, wears purple thunder to wreak havoc in the small and narrow space, explodes a big hole to come this underground rock layer directly, one on the left and other on the right attacks from both sides me with [Judgement] start.

No matter I also that many, great die , to continue to reactivate is, focused my firepower on [Judgement] completely is right.

Cooldown passes bit by bit, the fierceness of [Judgement] roars transformation gradually for the miserable howling sound, he could not resist my attack, but I depend upon to attack the returning blood of [Judgement] to provide own restoration, resists attack that wears, unexpectedly will can maintain this to balance, so long as I stop the hand to start all-out attack [Judgement], a second of output at least in thousand above, is very terrifying!

Quick, HP of [Judgement] less than 15%, has roared to start the big move, probably is the skill that Wan Jian returns to the birth family and so on, but is also very ordinary to my output, disregards it , to continue maintains my swift and fierce attack!

„Your highness, I am not perhaps good” [Judgement] face whiten.

Wears one to grasp the sword, is grasping Lei Guang, to I cause a ton damage at the same time, said: „Do not give up, the reinforcements arrived immediately, don't worry, you will certainly not die here!”

„Yes, Your highness!”

I slightly stare, reinforcements? What thing that is, we now in a place bottom 6000 + meters depth, what thing but also there is able to arrive here? Thousand strange are impossible, their tentacles apparently do not have my double sword to be sharp, cannot break through the zenith dome.

At this moment, suddenly behind transmits „rustling sound” the sound, a head searched, somewhat looks familiar, carefully looks, is the spirit umbrella insect, I go, will this gadget dig unexpectedly also a hole?

The body week, was fought in the prototype space that the Dou Qi class attacks, was the spirit umbrella insect appeared everywhere, on wall dense and numerous hole holes, was the spirit flowered insects appeared, ended, wore as if also understands that the player most feared anything, unexpectedly offered a sacrifice to the monster of spirit flowered insect large explosion rank!

However, I the entire attribute promote 150% now, was equal to wearing two -and-a-half sets of overlord coverall, did not fear!

Several spirit flowered insects approach me rapidly, explodes directly, the body transmits pain slightly, before was not that rending ache.

„67818!”

„61981!”

„69182!”

Saw that this injury digit I secretly laughed, along with the entire attribute promotion, my defensive power and magic defense significantly has also promoted, the spirit flowered insect sold at a discount to my injury greatly, does not have to be so fearful!

Lifts the hand is one set of skill loses, on the spirit flowered insect that has not exploded has absorbed many HP actually, their people the more better, my to exceed can buy in magnanimous HP.

Wears as if also discovered that the situation is not right, immediately shouted to clear the way lowly: „Your this group of idiots, his equipment has the special charm, can absorb the life, immediately begins using the ejection way to bomb him, [Judgement], your long-distance [Judgement], should not be attacked by him again.”

„Yes, Your highness!”

But I stare, what meaning is the long-distance ejection?

Quick, spirit flowered insect fluttering to the spirit umbrella insect, the spirit umbrella insect Jie Jie's scream, the tail have been raising high, the body is curving, the coccygeal vertebra has fluttered the spirit flowered insect, afterward crazy was roaring, made an effort to move the end, immediately an only spirit flowered insect just liked shell rumbling, NND, but can also such play?

This time absolutely did not have the [Drain] opportunity, my HP brushed to fall!

Present Hybrid Demon wore resorted to all means simply, abandoned the Hybrid Demon king to be proper completely, killing me has put the first place, was too practical, even if were her soul is not wears, but this strategy actually absolutely came from Huppe, this also let my confidence, the soul that wore had not been swallowed, certainly also in this body, but was hidden.

Flies high to start [Assault], locks [Judgement], must massacre him first, otherwise the spirit flowered insect must teach me to cultivate the behavior quickly!

[Judgement] also somewhat cannot choose the exact way because of flurry, unexpectedly is raising the long sword, did not give a thought to oneself god level BOSS dignity to enter the zenith dome the opening to re-enter the purgatory, what made him not think, the rock of zenith dome had the self- repair effect, we have fought here for nearly 20 minutes, the following channel has only closed the remaining radius 20 centimeters is less, such small obvious load bearing his huge form.

„This”

Purple Lei Guang does in a big way, I have not paid attention to the attack that wears, almost the double sword locks [Judgement].

One the method skill loses on [Judgement], his HP also instantaneously fell suddenly, was less than 10 minutes, the miserable howling body exploded, pile of equipment goods in airborne fell disorderly, I not slightly hesitant, put out a hand to hold to admit the package on 11, has not let off, in the meantime, the ear heard ting

„Bites!”

System announcement: Players 【Xiao Yao Zi Zai】 Kills one of the Hybrid Demon kings successfully 【[Judgement]】, Obtains the reward: Level + 4, charm value + 180, gold coin several + 1000000!

[Judgement] died, gives my reward to make up for my falling level to lose, and 180 charm value and thousand gold coin was Bai Zhuan!

Does not need to prolong contact!

I changed into the time to jump to fire into the space situation together, the double sword raised, the whole person presented the helix dances in the air cutting, like was an excavator of destroying the hardest defenses has fired into the surface.

Transmits sound that wore: „Li Xiao Yao, you think really can one live is leaving here?”

#1223: Murders the master

In the city wall, Stella was a claw passed over gently and swiftly, swept one group of player and NPC army falls under the city, part was swallowed, horrible to look.

„Mother!”

Death God’s Elegy is raising the lance, consecutively for three assassinations falls while the opportunity that Stella attacks on its macrobrachia, were too what a pity few to the attack damage that Stella caused, HP that insufficiently Stella's formidable vitality restored radically.

Old K also raises Axe also to remain to continue to fight, but Xue Rou actually raised is turning over to the Yuan sword to pass over gently and swiftly, said loudly: „You not awfully? Retreats!”

Although Matcha is only an elder, but in the [Zhan Long] status absolutely not less than vice- Guildmaster, the prestige under Li Mu and Yue Qing Qian, after all, her CBN rank was really not too high, in addition the fame of small monster, nobody will disrespect her several points, after all the man most feared that what woman, one type was the respected woman, another type was extremely the woman of loathing, the last type was to hit woman, Xue Rou status in [Zhan Long] male player mind was first type and last a set.

Li Mu raises the long sword to ride the dragon to meet head-on, consecutively for several times flies high to divide to cut the bang in the top of the head of giant beast, but the effect is not good, Wang Jian also rides the dragon maneuver in another side, shields under the [Zhan Long] player the city wall to retreat, at this moment, obtained retreating news Tu Long Fort randomly has become one group, in the city the player pushed a piece, the rear player has not obtained the news still to enter, Cooldown randomly became pot gruel.

The greedy desire drinks the fire most to like this scene, raises flame Axe to slaughter in the city, Sif is also same, having the strength of golden extermination back and forth to gallop in the crowd the rush, meets no resistance.

Let all players not think that the edition activity of struggle of this time Tu Long, we just have the superiority in most recent several hours, but now, actually turned into a slaughtered side.

„Roar! Roar!”

Stella is probably roaring because of the severe pain of abdomen, opens the big mouth suddenly, the spiral storm started, held the airborne red dragon flour, ended, Li Mu must be eaten!

„It is not wonderful!” Wang Jian said loudly: „Boss, your you must end the calf!”

Li Mu grabs the reins, the order red dragon flour of going all out flies away, but can also fly, is sweating: „Who shields my?”

Airborne Long Xiao, the top of the head of silver dragon passing over gently and swiftly giant beast, a beautiful form carried on the back to fly from the silver dragon, was Lin Wan Er, she flew high is a beautiful woman art of dancing energy!

„MISS!”

What a pity, the dizziness was given MISS by king BOSS unexpectedly!

Yue Qing Qian has a look at airborne Li Mu, has a look at me, said: „Brother Xiao Yao, cannot rescue Li Mu again, otherwise you will also die, a bit faster walks, after Li Mu dies, we set up a stone monument and make to him the Buddhist ceremony on the line”

Airborne Li Mu heard Yue Qing Qian saying that immediately soon cried.

My complexion is pale, hurried [say / way]: „Matcha, shields Qing Qian to retreat, I rescue Li Mu, you walk quickly!”

„? Brother Xiao Yao”

Yue Qing Qian also wants to say anything, was actually plundered by Xue Rou, held to rush to the city to go on the horseback, Xue Rou worked is never loathsome, because she knows that loathsome instead will implicate more people, in this point Qing Qian must learn from her.

But do I rescue Li Mu that soon will be swallowed?

My [Binding Chains] definitely also will be not necessarily able to the king by the skills of MISS , 100% attack effective, that only then another method pain!

Under very simple, formidable sensation of pain, even if king level BOSS laxly will also attack, making Li Mu organically be possible to take advantage that escapes, right, is now!

But under wanting this decision is very embarrassing, because the following forms of defensive action are really not I like!

The arm trembled, jumps to rush to the city wall, changed into together the time direct impact on Stella's abdomen, right, I must sneak in his belly, used the double sword to twist to break to pieces his intestines in inside, such came Li Mu to run away the birth day!

The [Wall of Dou Qi] in addition holds successfully, comes [Frost Armor] Armor again, the body in the airborne screw rotation, the double sword just liked the pointed cone pricked in Stella's abdomen, then, the surroundings already a blood and intestines of piece of warming up, were good because, [Frost Armor] Armor was the Frost self-satisfied technique, iced Armor to condense in body week about 5 cms away, separated Stella's flesh and blood, condensed a guard shield for me imperceptibly, otherwise I must, fly in circles by Stella's these intestines hotly anything died disgustingly.

Cutting!

Cuts again!

My unceasing strangles to death in Stella's abdomen flight, double sword heartless wielding, large intestines, caeca and duodenum what hews two completely, the personal appearance flies unceasingly upwardly, right, the heart of long jab giant beast, crushed its heart to be able to strike to massacre this giant beast, should that be the absolute weakness attacks?

Hundred thunder clouds storm erupts in Stella within the body, kills him to reach 30% HP directly, if I can tear into shreds its heart, can perhaps the second kill it really?

However, I as if think too simply, when I run out of the lobe of the lung of giant beast, saw that a giant heart in „ping” is beating, my heartbeat also speedily intensifies, simultaneously in the team channel broadcasts the Lin Wan Er sound: „Pig head, Li Mu and Wang Jian have gotten out of trouble, you also a bit faster walk, hurry up, Sif, and qin song arrived, the distant place also sees a huge corona the person's shadow, should be the dark blue billows comes personally!”

„Knew, you remove first, I come immediately!”

Said superficially, but I actually under Yu Jingtao the hundred zhang (333m), the dark blue billows personally did not come, struggle of edition this time Tu Long we must be defeated!

Raises the double sword, the attack, locks the goal Stella's heart!

Moreover, the line start I strongest two moves, ride the wind to cut [Strength of a Thousand Men]!

The golden ray shoots up to the sky, erupts two moves in Stella's within the body directly, altogether 20 swords cut the attack to penetrate the heart of giant beast, but did not have that effect that I imagined, around Stella's heart presented an energy cover, protected the heart not to be attacked, my these 20 attacks surpassed the most injury to fall by the immunity.

However, this guard shield is not multipurpose, rides the wind Ling Lie the sword air/Qi that cuts to cut to pieces as before the heart surface meat level, can see that blood were spattering in all directions.

Continues to cut to strike!

A spin body, gathers full strength, is cutting of round violent storm kills, the double sword is shaking the heart energy cover unceasingly, wipes out its toughness unceasingly, most in five minutes, this Stella will definitely die in my sword gets down!

That heart soon had been slivered the scalloped kidney shape by me, the surface layer completely is the overlapping earthworm sword mark, the flesh lump turns, if the oil used such one presses out, then added the onion ginger and pepper is a trough extremely delicious stir-frying scalloped kidney.

I do not know why I can also think to eat at this time, thinks that ate the belly a little to be unexpectedly hungry, at this time wished one could a palm of the hand to pull out itself, too does not make every effort to succeed simply!

When I cut fiercely strikes Stella abdomen, suddenly behind transmits together the familiar golden light, Sif came, that is her extermination strength!

„Buzz!”

The long sword flood moves the golden ray, Sif is flushing to come horizontally, the corners of the mouth are having the scowl: „Brat, what you want to make to my adorable small pet, do you want to massacre it?”

My moral nature trembled, ended, strategic defeat!

Leaves to walk, opens invincible Cooldown to be insufficient, with the words of overlord rebirth, must die in ten times to massacre Stella here, has been unworthy, moreover I did not determine that was the death can also get online, if died to be transmitted Tian Ling Empire unable to participate in the struggle of following activity Tu Long, that ended.

However Sif as if not want to ask me such to leave, after is the rapid fierce sword.

Is listening to the rumor, my turning around standard keeps off suddenly, „clang” does to swing directly Sif's long sword the sword, left hand butterfly sword rapid [Combo] starts, 7 golden six glow stars flee on the sword blade edge, has given Sif 7 attacks.

„!”

Sif lifts the hand to cover the palm on my breastplate, the corners of the mouth are bringing grinning fiendishly: „Brat, tumbles out the body of my small pet to go, do not disturb here!”

„Hong!”

The formidable strength almost imprisons me instantaneously, Sif pushes me to dash backward, rips open Stella's flesh and blood directly, the next quarter hits again in within the body outer covering of giant beast, „bang” hits directly thoroughly, outside bright, but my whole body was painful as if disperses has put up generally, HP also only remaining 25%, NND, assassinated the duty to be defeated really!

Must walk!

Does not wait for the Sif next attack, I opened body of effect 25 seconds of invincible not extinguishing directly, increases speed to 100%, no matter Sif's attack, flew directly to the East of Tu Long Fort.

Sif is in an uncontrollable rage, but also discovers my invincible effect, therefore has not continued to chase down, instead flew high to dive, kills the players and NPC in city.

The distant place, [Zhan Long], [Legend], [Hero’s Mound] and other Guild the players are retreating fighting, the situation is less optimistic, massive Hybrid Demon entered the city, Stella is destroying entire Tu Long Fort crazily, the dark blue billows have not committed fortunately suicide, otherwise feared Tu Long Fort to degenerate into a cemetery instantaneously.

„Be careful, the greedy desire drank the fire to come!”

Yue Qing Qian said in the guild channel loudly: „Multipurpose control skills, be not thinking massacres him , to continue to retreat, do not stay, making in the member of canyon also retreat, retreats to cold uncultivated land Dragon’s den, the middle road section does not have the danger to defend, we can whole army has been annihilated.”

The Qing Qian strategic vision is good, saw this point.

I continue to proceed to fly, simultaneously shakes the body, shakes completely residual Stella's mucilage, the lowering the head bird's eye view earth, Tu Long Fort had half to be invaded by Hybrid Demon . Moreover, massive BOSS level Hybrid Demon appeared near the East city wall, has been slaughtering the player and NPC army, the entire tactical situation to us has missed the extreme.

Not far away, Lin Wan Er is riding Little Bai, said: „Pig, downward do not look that walks quickly?”

„, Why?”

I in consternation, vision cannot help but continue to glance toward the city on, actually saw has hit hard the mind

Wears raises the long sword to stand on the East city wall, the surroundings are the corpse of player, above the sword blade edge are reappearing all purple Lei Guang, but in her right hand, actually proposes one to Ran Jiebai the head, is hundred!

Murders the master!

#1246: Defeats the god to honor again

Next day, in the morning early wakes up.

Also is the sumptuous breakfast, eats very full, because knows that at noon did not have Cooldown offline to look for food mostly.

„Brushes!”

Gets online, appears in black flame city, place that I get online in palace, a blue ray lingers in all around, the 1 second of getting online enters by the protective condition, is unable to be attacked, but along with the field of vision clear this condition automatically by the detachment, not far away, two was also ridden the warhorse the powder spirit guards to clash, said flustered: „Sir, is not good!”

„How?” I asked.

And a [say / way]: „Venerable to lead his troops to Xin god already outside soldier Lincheng, threatened that must revenge for good friend Kress, was clamoring is making the Sir go out of town to meet head-on, otherwise he trampled flat the entire black flame city!”

„, Who to Xin is?” I am confused.

He explained: „Is the person who yesterday's Kress god Venerable to run away to request reinforcements, Venerable to Xin god with Sir Kress is always on good terms!”

„So that's how it is.”

I show a faint smile, draw out the butterfly sword, said: „Guides, I go to be able this to leave Xin, having a look at this god to honor many skills!”

Will leave, suddenly in the corner broadcasts a sound: „Sir.”

Turns around to look, actually the discovery is Iraqi Wei, that by the young lady who Kress grabs, finally after Kress was massacred by me, she lived in the black flame city, clothing was neat, looks like has not received anything to encroach, but behind with a guard, thinks that was Luo Zao remains her, awaited my „punishing”.

„How, Iraqi Wei?” I asked.

She is nipping the red lip, starts to speak but hesitates, will say several seconds later: „Past I followed the father practiced to see this to leave Xin, what he practiced was the space principle, can kill people in invisible, the Sir please probably be careful! Is inferior to Kress to Xin's strength, but he wants Kress to want fearful ten times absolutely!”

Originally to remind me, probably Iraqi Wei now also thought that I am a good person, did not think me dead in battle, otherwise she must become to Xin's spoils of war, which the fate also very to went certainly.

I nod, say with a smile: „Relax, I will have to have!”

Outside the palace, Luo Zao in the fitting out troops, 100 + has dispersed the spirit level heavy cavalry preparation to finish, has held up the war flag of black flame city high, crowded around me to move toward the city gate, the black flame city was not big, after five minutes, arrived in the city gate, in the city was standing many guards, at daggers drawn, as if outside invading one's territory with city soon have joined battle.

„”

The front door opens slowly, I in summon raspberry entered thousand frost wing effects instantaneously, the whole person takeoffs one meter gradually to flutter, outside the city, full was the troops, was holding high the black flag, in the crowd dead ahead, was one wears the Chinese-style gown, looked like the person of features suggesting extraordinariness and immortality, this person to Xin? It looks like the reversed image is an obtaining enlightenment elder!

Luo Zao and the others progress to follow slowly, afterward is away from me about 50 meters place to halt, said: „Sir, the god Venerable the fight, others cannot intervene, end will wait for the human here to aid the Sir!”

„Um.”

I also know that these subordinates actually in waiting to be deciding a victory and defeat, who has won with anyone, does not need to honor the battle to make contact with an own poor life for the god, in this person of boundary made the city innumerably, the quantity that the god Venerable not 1000 also several hundred, thinks that every day will have such duel?

Fight other people who the gods revere can not intervene, have such custom, the player enters the person boundary to obtain the godship, must depend on Shan Tiao mostly, thinks that also is really cruel, is makes the player accompany these BOSS to send Cooldown simply.

Flutters to Xin's long gown slowly, features suggesting extraordinariness and immortality visits me, said lightly: „Was boy, you have killed Kress? That is a god Venerable, what despicable method you used to kill him, and seized his city?”

I think funny, lifts the hand to draw out the long sword, said: „What method with, has not defeated him, what's wrong, can you to leave Xin take revenge? That comes, let alone rubbish.”

In any case is a war, said that too does not help matters.

This was enraged by me to Xin instantaneously, puts out a hand in airborne to grasp, immediately a green musical instrument appears in his hands, is that a suona? Cannot, have the suona in this potential surface unexpectedly, is this must blow the deceased person?

The next quarter, makes me know that to Xin this odd hypothesis actually strong fearfulness, he started to play the suona, but the sound was not unexpectedly coarse, on the contrary was somewhat melodious, the sound trembled suddenly becomes the firm friendship calls, quite some iron Markin feelings, at this moment, the air position twisted, a round invisible blade layer on layer has hit my abdomen!

„261828!”

Really, striking power does not have Kress to be so high, but attacks almost invisible, is unable to defend with square keeps off!

Cannot sit waiting for death!

I flushed suddenly, single-handed distant, [Great Realm of Desolation] locking leaves Xin!

„Bang!”

In numerous violent engine knocks, has not caused the too strong damage unexpectedly, he used the space magic to form one to protect the shield in the surroundings! For a penny and for a pound, I opened shield of near body stars to fight!

„!”

The space twists once more, this time I have sentence in advance, is sideways to keep off the shield of stars suddenly in the front, the arm shakes, two invisible space shock-wave hits on the shield of stars, but my butterfly also layer on layer pricks in his protecting shield, carries over the [Strength of a Thousand Men] effect, hits including the disappearing belt, the bang draws back several steps to Xin continually, blew the movement of suona also slightly to stagnate.

Good, the attack can break his release magic, this is easy to do!

I secretly rejoice, however the next quarter had proven I wrong must be odd, passed over gently and swiftly to Xin corners of the mouth wipes the happy expression, suddenly the suona left the mouth, the left hand fist, roars, all around wind blade edge dance, my body cannot move unexpectedly instantaneously, next quarter by invisible space magics swallowing!

„371272!”

Fearful, this also?!

Carefully looked at one, this skill was called „distortion field of force”, next time will pay attention!

Draws back dozens meters continually, the [Cleansing Rain] technique returns to the blood, fills next health potion, summoned Ancient Heavenly Tiger to lead a cheer, but the small tiger at all was not a match, 2-3 made into the remnant blood hum to run, but I have also established [Azure Dragon Crossbow] while this Cooldown, the destiny card sign turned, treads the [Seven Stars Teleportation] position to start [Assault]!

„Bang!”

The numerous hits, the [Assault] skill creates 1 second of dizziness effect, rides the wind to cut to make use to go, creates the fearful injury digit continuously, wipes out to Xin HP large scale also attracts many HP for me, the instantaneous full blood, this made me confident, can fight again! The shield of summon stars, adopts „walks to chop” skill to gather round this obtaining enlightenment elder to output unceasingly, simultaneously I also note, so long as I appear in his, can cause his magic to lose the focal point, the space magic of released directly was broken.

Therefore, this showdown became extremely has the technicality, I circled the walk position attack, avoided his magic unceasingly, was not stupid to Xin, frequently a twinkle appeared in the distant place, was separated from my diversion, afterward was a wave of large-scale magic attack, but this magic and second could not massacre me, were chased down by me on the contrary retreat in defeat again and again, HP also little falling.

As for the distortion field of force, cools Cooldown is 35 seconds, this could determine, before his next distortion field of force starts I tread the [Seven Stars Teleportation] position to avoid, this lets be mad to Xin trembles, turned into one type to devastate with my fight for him, this is insults to one that the god Venerable absolutely, even his subordinates also certainly thought that their god Venerable the tactic is suppressed.

Does not have the means that the attribute is a kingly way, I have [Drain] and other special effect, but can also repel, this leaves Xin is BOSS of mage department, the strength value is inferior to me, therefore the repelling effect of blade edge of champion became especially remarkable, when 50% probability attacks repelled the interruption magic, 10% probability dizziness, were circled by me to Xin who again walked to chop is almost at wit's end!

More panic-stricken should be Iraqi Wei, Luo Zao and the others, they have probably not seen such god to honor the fight, in their eyes the omnipotent space principle god Venerable to Xin, now actually plays with by me in applauses, does not have the strength to hit back, all skills were eaten by me stubbornly, must blame only to blame his strength me high, the magic second unable to massacre me, this two are indispensable.

Once grasped know-how, fight also became very simple, near 40 minutes, had only been cut by me to Xin's blood strip remaining about 2%, I had a look at the skill, the destiny card sign and ride the wind to cut CD to be good, in addition one set of can combo, almost the second massacre this BOSS?

Was roaring to Xin angrily, actually did not help matters, the strength that escaped continually did not have, the body was put down by me continuously chops to repel, dizziness, he had certainly any escaping skill, but simply does not have the opportunity to use now.

At this moment, suddenly has after death broadcast Iraqi Wei's voice: „Sir, please do not kill to Xin!”

„Why?” I questioned.

Iraqi Wei said: „My father Nike was imprisoned by Kress in some mystical deep deep pool, but nobody knows where is, this is in cahoots to Xin and Kress, he definitely knows where the father was imprisoned, where asking the Sir to ask this deep deep pool for Iraqi Wei.”

I knit the brows: „Said me to help your reason.”

Iraqi Wei is nipping the silver tooth, said: „Father followed the father's younger brother to go to the boundary, he knows that the way of boundary, can lead the god king who you look for the boundary, completes your dream!”

Hears here, I put out a hand to hold to Xin's arm immediately, the strength of left hand imperial day start, grab them to be used to lock in the chains of mount giant beast, will leave Xin's arm to bundle solid, said: „Sends under custody to return to the city!”

To a Xin face shame, does not have the strength to hit back.

As for army that leaving Xin brings, was disbanded together, allowing them to enter the words of black flame city to be able with Luo Zao and the others to form two parties inevitably, when the time comes the battle will get up not to be good, after all I cannot stay here, but must enter the boundary to meet the meeting god king, must make the black flame city stabilize, such Dong Cheng Yue found the black flame city time can attain the lower position god godship.

#1248: The weak one of the boundary

Delayed for nearly 3 hours in the game, finally the strength of old Nike recovered much, prepares the luggage, stepped with me together to the battle path of boundary, naturally, his duty is responsible for delivering to the boundary entrance, after entering boundary that was I rushed, after I entered the boundary, mostly will again not return to the person boundary, if after all I flew upwards, that must comply with this custom, the god emperor can not enter the boundary, the god king can not enter the person boundary, the god could not revere to enter the ground, otherwise bad the custom will have encountered chases down.

In the dim light of night, two person's shadows have grazed the low altitude, I fly quite well, the body of Nike has not recovered completely, the speed cannot follow me completely.

„Entrance where?” I asked.

„Very burning hot place.” Nike shows a faint smile.

„Can burning hot?” I continue to ask.

„Roasts ashes the body sufficiently.” He said.

I was silent.

After how many minutes, we stay in one are spurting the crater front of lava, active volcano, is this wants the barbecue the rhythm? My unbelievable referring to fire mountain pass, said: „Do not tell me the entrance of boundary under this.”

„Right.” Said: „Space between person boundary and boundary maintains is the superhigh temperature, such temperature makes practice degree mean people unable to enter the boundary, only then adopted the test of rock magma to match is the god king, this was also basically tests.”

I am Yang Yanji the strength, the body and spirit practice incomparably intrepidly, and Yang Yanzhen is mad protects the body not to fear the high temperature, but in the game other said that draws out the double sword slowly, perhaps if as expected, has the manufacture flying upwards difficulty monster by broken lonesome god urogenous crater, I do not want dead in inside.

„Do you go in me together?” I turn around to ask Nike.

Nike shakes the head, says with a smile: „Sir, my body and strength have not restored, the scalding hot lava will turn into the flying ash the old bones my this, the Sir you are certainly careful, in lava level also some small devils.”

„What is that?”

„Lava insect, takes swallowing lava as the insect of lifestyle, their attacks are sharp, many gods Venerable in the process of flying upwards by the lava insect massacring, you were also careful, after all you he have a look at my body now”, said: „After all now has as before is every body, perhaps basic is unable to endure including lava heat degree.”

„This you can feel relieved.” My slightly smile: „You go back, perhaps soon after I will again come to here.”

„Yes, I will await calmly the Sir to visit in the black flame city with Iraqi Wei!”

„Um.”

Deeply inspires, I no longer hesitate anything, jumped to clash, as before, left hand, Huaguang bloomed, stars flat lands raised the condensation for the shield of stars, protected my body to clash!

„Tittered!”

Although the rock magma under my impulse has not contacted me, but the feelings of some saunas, lift the shield of stars to fire into the volcano as before rapidly the deep place, at first fortunately, the ignition effect creates to me every second several thousand injuries, but can also withstand, the speed of afterward flying was hindered by the rock magma, can only maintain 30% speeds to fly, the body was surrounded by the rock magma, causes about every second of thousand damage instantaneously, very awfully!

I can only depend upon imperial day to push the rock magma to the body forcefully, maintains certain field of vision by oneself, after all buries and in the rock magma cannot open eyes, was needless to say without field of vision words anything.

„Chirp chirp”

The lava insect came, is one is only similar to the thing of mouse, but the whole body is red, gnawed to the shield and my armor stars, the striking power was not weak, is equal to 9 levels of Hybrid Demon levels.

„Go away!”

Instantaneous [Tempest Sword], chops again [Strength of a Thousand Men], the resorption many HP, continued actually maintains the submersions of body, this feeling is unendurable, as if each quarter will be massacred general!

The lava insect gnawed unceasingly, the shield of stars soon broke, but looked on the map, as if map ZONE knot also soon arrived, at present, presented a blood red big net suddenly, was ties!

„Bang!”

When I hit above, the whole body transmits the tear ache, NND, but can also come hardly? Nike that old boy has not told here also such hard knot!

Are not many thinks, attack!

The [Combo] [Strength of a Thousand Men] bang exits together, „” in great online leaves behind sword marks, but this standing net is tenacious, undergoes such attack not to be as before broken , to continue to attack! Rides the wind to cut to rumble swiftly and fiercely, as before broken, hits again, has rumbled crazily for nearly two minutes, during this, depends on the [Cleansing Rain] technique + to drink health potion to restore completely, even was forced to use including eternal boundary super skill of abstention of order conservation, finally, this knot was broken a hole hole by me, the diving posture had overrun, NND, almost died in inside!

Enters the boundary at the same time I secretly have been rejoicing, luckily I am the Heavy Armor department, if I am the legal system, with gathering [Magic Shield] can support nearly 10 minutes of suffering in volcano really? This flying upwards fairyland edition Taikeng father, simply was the nightmare of all Mage, archer and assassin, does not know what to do really Wan Er entered in this map should, she indeed was the entire clothing first assassin, but the physique was placed there after all, can attain the godship really?

Cannot help but somewhat worried.

At present as before a darkness, are the night of boundary, but I that straight from the sky is standing, this is not good, very easily becomes the goal that others hunt and kill, hurries to go to the ground, hides in the jungle is the kingly way!

Bends down to change into the meteor to overrun together, the recent map is a piece of green jungle, and cannot see any lights, is really a good place!

„Crash-bang!”

Has hit certain branches, enters the thick patch of grass technique stealth the condition, has a look at the surrounding map, almost does not have a thing in the world, anything cannot see.

Looks up to the sky, this time saw the heavenly bodies unexpectedly, was really rare, and air as if want compared with the person boundary freshly, this was not the illusion, the human in the air of boundary flood the rich death and blood smell, but Jigyeong-ri did not have, did the rare god king really revere to strive to excel that many compared with the god?

Thinks that here somewhat is excited, challenges the god king, captures the godship! Really a thrilling matter.

Goes through in the jungle fast, I must seek for a city, where has the place of city to know the god kings, otherwise looked like a fly equally randomly to proceeding along no particular course.

Is walking, the East daybreak daybreak, suddenly the distant place has heard a roar of wild animal.

„”

A head length mammoth was miserably howling to clash, the back was pricked a handle lance, on the body was inserting the dense and numerous arrow arrows, was transmits the sound of voices and noise of hoofbeat and crowd, some did here also people hunt unexpectedly?

„Your highness, you, we cannot follow you slowly!”

In the shout, wore the youth in Jinjia to raise the lance and bow and arrow to clash, an excitement of face, laughed: „Hurry up, today will hunt and kill this growing hair great shape, the father will not say that my military force was mediocre, your this crowd of lazy goods, will walk actually a bit faster, did your equestrian skills waste on the belly of woman?”

Your highness?

Is this imperial prince? Looks at the appearances of some makings actually very official's second generations, has not thought of me, as soon as after entering this potential surface, met the honored person.

About 20 + people of convoy guards flushed, are nervous, for fear that this your highness has an accident.

I still stand on a limb of tree, static visits them to hunt, simultaneously in the mind actually full is speechless, this what's the matter, is unreasonable!

The group of people of present, do not have one unexpectedly are BOSS, even if that your highness, is NPC of Titan level, my one set of skill can the second of killing goods, this mortal appear in Jigyeong-ri, isn't this boundary the domain that the god king lives? This did explain?

At this time, your highness is a lance projects, „tittering” entered among the napes of the neck of mammoth, the blood chaotic wind, the mammoth roared to fall to the ground, was killed.

Before one group of bodyguards overtake, pants: „Your highness, you have killed the mammoth personally, this king will certainly make you follow great nation Master Xuewu!”

„Ha!” Imperial prince self-satisfied laughing of: „That is the great nation masters, but a god king, following him to practice, certainly quickly can obtain the strength of god.”

„Subordinates in advance congratulated your highness here!”

In this time, a bodyguard is raising the long bow suddenly, loudly was shouting to clear the way to my direction: „Anyone, comes out to me, I induced to your breath, came out quickly!”

Was discovered?

I have not hidden, jump to leap to set up.

This bodyguard looks at my terse equipment in consternation, said: „Who are your you?”

I: „Initially to expensive boundary, I from person boundary.”

„Does god revere?” He visits me, suddenly taunted smiled, said: „On you absolutely does not have a godship strength, unexpectedly dares to say one are from the person boundary, snort, is really person of the gaining fame by deceiving people, your below a few words want to say that admires the prestige of your highness, subordinates who wants to join your highness for Turin empire potency?”

„Turin empire?” I cannot bear smile: „Can consider.”

„Bold!”

This bodyguard held a sword to clash, the imperial prince has not stopped, thinks that wants to have a look at my strength.

I for fear that strike to massacre this am only the NPC bodyguard of elite rank, turns the skill, the sword blade edge hangs upside down, directly with the sword hilt attack, the standard parry that pushes directly into his sword blade edge, the sword hilt fierce hit on his shoulder, stumbles its bang on a wryneck subtree, landing in an extremely difficult situation, spits blood to continue, was too weak!

Emperor's son's eyes have shone instantaneously, said: „Who are your you?”

„When I am a hobo.”

„Hobo gentleman, you may be willing to return to the capital city in Turin empire along with me together, I will report you to the father, your strength is powerful, I have witnessed with own eyes.”

„Many thanks your highness, I wants.” Is exactly as one wishes, I want to go to be able that great nation master!

#1261: Reentry day boundary

Next day, obtains the latest news, the sky roses and ancient musical scales and remnant dream three people enters the boundary, and after experiencing for 14 hours meets, challenged to massacre a god king together, in the fight the remnant dream died in battle, but the sky rose obtained in one god godship, later, the sky rose flew upwards, the ancient musical scale challenged another god king to be defeated after the later 3 hours, was killed to be lost in thought.

In addition, demon mountain, brown pupil and maplewood are drunk three people also the bitter experience defeat in the boundary, was challenging in the fight of god king to be massacred completely, even if it seems like were the top player runs into the god king also to kneel, only if looked like the player of my this high [Drain], the high output and high reply to be able with god Wang Dantiao, otherwise raised does not need to raise.

Afterward in several day, Matcha, Li Mu, Wang Jian, Old K and other [Zhan Long] the players entered broken lonesome god one after another, moreover everyone has had custom-made the goal to oneself, the Matcha goal was the god godship, Li Mu, Wang Jian and Old K only strives for massacring the god to honor first, flies upwards said again, when Level has come up, then entered the broken lonesome god promotion to be OK.

But like my this type wants to stutter the fatty is really rare, once so long as has succeeded, then on the prize investment, the superior god godship has seven, killed one few one, the selective wait words possibly this village did not have this shop.

Waits painstakingly for 4 days, finally, I waited till System Notification to enter broken lonesome god once more news.

Does not worry, first satisfactory sleeping, was satiated with food and wine next day has gotten online again!

In the morning, Wan Er and East city bound the apron to play the role of the beautiful female cook to make the breakfast, I ate do not know the taste, looks the female servant who two young ladies has installed, afterward got online, drafts the war-god territory!

„Brushes!”

Gets online, takes out from the warehouse prepares the good thing, card 20 +, includes that purgatory ghost the card, I Ching pill two, in addition many compounded drug and micro equipment repair oil, brought fully the thing, flying upwards god stone.

The second time, light gate familiar road.

After a ray, I already appeared in the broken lonesome god surface, does not waste Cooldown, seeks the surrounding brook, found the later diving to enter, is similar to at the forum said that as long as is in the ground has the water place, explained that under enters the entrance of person boundary, waste Cooldown are not many, fast entered a person of boundary.

The domain of person boundary is not general big, city over a thousand, black flame city that I do not know first coming where, therefore does not look, from the sky soars directly, seeks crater, looked for nearly one hour, finally in the distant place sees the flame column that soars to the heavens, during a crater is erupting, did not fear, on!

„Buzz!”

Holds up the shield of stars, the whole person is crashing into the volcano rapidly, coming is the scalding hot lava, I do not have the stay has attacked downward, finally arrived in a knot between person of boundary and boundary, immediately breaks it, direct impact on the sky of boundary, „brushing” a Pure Brightness, arrives at present has had not seen you for a long time the boundary.

Turns on the map, anything could not see that can only look, because besides me basically on nobody since day boundary, therefore this entrance also can only look, but is unfamiliar with the people and place, therefore first went to the Turin empire to say again, the good and evil I was also the Great General in Turin empire, although currently very much has the possibility already by lu, after all I left the Turin empire 4 days, according to the game Cooldown conversion was 16 days.

„!”

The brushing sound of horsewhip transmits, a trade route harnessed the carriage to come by far, about 30 + people of appearances, on the freight vehicle were inserting the fresh flag, actually does not know that which empire belonged.

I non-stop fly, falls on the front of trade route suddenly.

„What person?”

Wears the fatty of Chinese dress to jump down the horse rapidly, said: „This brave warrior, are you?”

I said: „Does not need to fear that I am travel of inner ear, wants to ask the way.”

The fat people behind, two hands grasp the Axe military person to be then relaxed, looks at my equipment appearance, they also probably understand that radically was not the match, once hit, I destroyed completely their one group of people absolutely am not the issue, saying that the fatty was then all smile: „, Does not know that you do want to go?”

I said: „Turin empire.”

„, Turin empire? That must cross over the border” he to say astonished: „Are you really the person in Turin empire?”

„Yes, how?”

„Strange, Turin empire distance place is separated by two big empires, you can become lost unexpectedly here, can not be strange?”

„That Turin empire in what direction?”

„From here to east, about 400 li (0.5km) almost arrived, but wants the way ominous crow empire and blood tooth empire, these two empires esteem martial arts, everywhere is military who practices the feat of arms, and emperors in two big empires are the god kings, you are certainly careful, otherwise had much easily not.”

„Many thanks shows the way.”

I naturally did not worry that will be killed, now is god Wang to come challenges, I can massacre greatly and that's the end.

If this self-confident does not have continually, I do not need to challenge the god emperor.

„Bang!”

Rises straight from the ground, the ground has left behind a cyclone, has left behind trade route of one crowd of staring dumbfounded, they have probably not seen the follower who has been able to fly, because in their cognition, only then god Wang Cai will fly, but is the present person, the god king?

I naturally do not pay attention to them to think anything, but straight flew to east, increases speed the peak, the whole person has reached the limit of speed.

Near two hours of flights, enter in the Turin empire, afterward asked the way, revised under one, flew again for nearly 20 minutes, a palatial city appears at present, has had not seen you for a long time the Turin city!

The Turin city restored tranquilly when the war, that several armies that the garrison outside city is I leave orders, and Wang Qi high hanging in the military compound, the imperial prince and king controlled the army life of entire empire finally.

Flies into the city from the space, directly soars the imperial prince palace.

„” Falls to the ground, a not far away maidservant had already recognized me, said with a smile pleasantly surprised: „Great General, is you? Does the Great General you come back?”

I nod: „Yes, leading me to see your highness!”

„Yes!”

The imperial prince compared more beaming more and buoyant past, and body the supernatural power cyclone, this made me be astonished on Monday very much: „Your highness, have you built godship?”

The imperial prince nods, immediately bends down to worship on bended knees in the place, said: „Many thanks the Great General, your good friend granted me a god to honor the had godship, therefore I have practiced for half a month diligently, finally promoted for the god Venerable!”

„Good, congratulated your highness!”

„Great General, you return to the empire, won't this time walk again?”

„No, I am only the way, the battle path as in the distant place.”

„?”

On the imperial prince face passed over gently and swiftly a disappointed look, said: „I lead you having an audience with father, he has been missing you!”

„Good.”

Quick, arrives above the main hall, the facial expression of king was also better, saw after me, immediately must seal to enjoy innumerably, even is willing to bestow my dozens to wait on concubine anything, thinks somewhat small excitedly is not willing to leave, but for the godship of god emperor, I cannot easy and comfortable leading a life of comfort here, must walk, asked the road of day boundary.

The king was all of a sudden astonished: „I and others are not god king, naturally does not understand how to go to the day boundary, moreover day boundary by seven big god emperor Military Control, our such mortals, even if were also difficult to run away since the day boundary dies.”

„Nobody knows how to go?” I am astonished however asked.

At this time, an old man held the fist in the other hand saying: „Your majesty, the old minister had heard actually goes to the legend of bygone days boundary.”

The king said: „Said?”

The old men said: „Hands down the day boundary is the genuine god territory, from bright potential surface, but Sun is the entrance of god territory, the daily first Xuyang penetration cloud layer time, the follower is moving to the sunlight direction, so long as speed breakthrough certain limit, can find the potential surface entrance, since day boundary, but this Cooldown is short, only then less than one minute, I think that the Great General must go to the words of day boundary, can try this method.”

I nod: „Good, understood!”

From the dawn also two hours, waits!

Said good-bye the imperial prince and king, this time walked, approximately, will not come again.

Found the mountain peak that quite stands tall and erect in the, sits waits for the sunrise above, patient, this is the first essential factor that each follower can practice, hasn't the patient person possibly had uncommon cultivation is?

In the first Xuyang ray injection view, I opened thousand frost wings, goes toward the direction rapid flight of Sun.

Also does not know that this means are reasonable, if that old fogy in deceiving me, I can only seek for another god king, after defeating him, forced him to say the means of day boundary.

„Whistling”

The bone-chilling cold morning breeze sways near the ear, my speed is getting more and more fast, but is only the flight, actually as before cannot see the entrance of day boundary, was deceived really?

When my speed close limit, suddenly at present „” had the transformation, that seven color dawns changed into the potential surface strength of innumerable grid shape, the present world also instantaneously twists, the entrance appeared , the innumerable roaring flame flaming are burning in all around, but the dead ahead is one transmits the luminous exit , the potential surface strength exceptionally twists violent, unceasing wreaks havoc my body, HP is brushing to fall, is really fearful!

„Buzz!”

The speed has crashed in entrance quickly certainly, at present suddenly bright, came, day boundary!

„Bang!”

A bang, I hit above a precipice, HP already fell about 20%, was good because of successfully since the day boundary, but I was located above a stretch of earth unexpectedly, initially the god emperor said the epizone I came time was not only then hung in the airborne city? What now this stretch of earth has is, comes to the wrong place?

„Whiz!”

I just am thinking, suddenly the broken rumor transmits, is the arrow arrow!

Quick of eye and hand, single-handed, grasps an arrow arrow of speedily flight directly in the hand, I am sideways to explode kick the rock to overrun with the strength, the left hand draws out to do the sword direct penetration together thick patch of grass, sword blade edge horizontally in the nape of the neck place of attack, but the leaf blade shakes, I actually saw an attractive cheek, in the hand have been grasping a cheap short bow, visits me astonished.

This is only a young girl of hunting, what's the matter?

#1262: The good person life is safe

„Few variants, under the sword are forgiving!”

Shouted, young girl, carries the bamboo basket and beard gray old man to grasp the small iron shovel to shout loudly: „Please careful, do not injure my granddaughter.”

I lower the head to have a look, was held the young girl of skill by me actually likely is the small beast that is unable to tame, has struggled furiously, and tries to pull out the short dagger of waist to puncture me.

„Snort?”

I visit her funnily, this young girl also really acts recklessly, takes advantage of opportunity such one lets go, immediately she obtained from you, a spin body draws out the dagger to assassinate, on the dagger is bringing incorruptible, has not thought that she started to practice young unexpectedly.

Young girls punctures is expected, I naturally cannot the move, left hand, in the palm emerge the innumerable stars, „buzz” formed the shield of stars, the dagger of young girl has broken off in the shield surface suddenly, soon will rebound to cause heavy losses to her moment I to receive the skill in the shield of stars, the giant light shield vanished instantaneously, young girl face backlash several steps with amazement.

The old men walked, to the back of the head of young girl is being a palm of the hand, scolds to shout to clear the way: „Doesn't dead girl, you want to live?”

The young girls are tender the sound track: „Grandfather, this person is so ominous, why you must hit me!”

The old men said: „Your this dead girl, you could not look that others did show mercy? Otherwise struck already wanted your poor life, you acted recklessly really!”

I turn over to the sheath the butterfly sword, shows a faint smile to ask: „Why can you shoot me?”

„You hide in the woods, I also think that you is a wild pig, therefore shot arrows.” Although she sound was gentle, appearance that but some do not concede as before.

The old men walk to go forward, look at a I armor, in the eye have several points to awe, said: „Do few variants, look at your attire certainly are not here person?”

„Um, I just came from boundary.”

„Are you a god king?”

„Temporarily is also not.”

The old men as if relaxed, said: „Since is not the god king, should understand that on this day the boundary is the domains of seven big god emperors, you come here are momentarily looked that you wrote off.”

„I did not fear that who you are?” I asked one.

The old men have gawked staring, afterward self-ridicules smiles: „We? We hunt for the slave.”

„Hunts for the slave, what is that?”

„Is” he is resigned-looking, said: „Is this potential surface status meanest humanity, the value that we have is to plant, hunts and catches fish, textile, provides all that the life needs for the upper boundary god clan.”

„Upper boundary?”

I knit the brows, already understood anything, said: „What you refer to is these floats in the airborne palace, in your eyes, are these people called the upper boundary god clans?”

„Yes.”

The old men nod, afterward lowers the sound, said: „The informer of god emperor is found in the entire world of mortals, few variants, we do not say here, if you do not shut out, returns to the village with us, the weather was late, night time will have patrols hunting to appear in the world of mortals, hunts and kills these night as before followers outside.”

„Has patrolling hunting for who the god Venerable the strength?”

„Yes, they are one group of bandits and thieves, disregards the world person three principles, while the night penetration potential surface, hunts and kills the powerhouse to supplement that promotes own spirit strength, even hunts for the slave not to let off.”

Has not thought that day boundary also has to patrol hunting, I nod saying: „Good, I follow you.”

The young girl visits me panting in indignation, has not spoken any excessive words again.

Although this is my second time comes the day boundary, but I do not know one where, does in Rome as Rome does understood first said again, is not killing Yun Qian in any case anxiously, completes the schoolwork is not the misdemeanor.

As the old person and his young girl return to the village, the old man hunted and killed a deer, but old is almost unable to move, is drags away, I cannot tolerate , helping him carry on the shoulder, on old person's face left a smile, the young girl also extinguished to my alert.

Returns to the small village time already darkness, night only in remaining villages fragmentary lights.

Old person's family is very crude, is only a thatched shed, has divided two rooms, young girl, old person, I must sleep in the street today mostly.

„”, Deer has placed on the sheet iron, this is a very lush deer, when the maturity, the meat are also many, the young girl looks at the deer, then has licked the lip, said: „Grandfather, today do we eat the deer bouillon?”

The old person spoils has caressed lightly her head, said: „Um, you cut off Lu Tou, is used to make the soup, then in takes the deer corpse to deliver to there, in tribute the game as us, otherwise, does not receive this month this month, perhaps our master grandson day will not feel better.”

The young girls dig the small mouth: „Is Lu Toutang, when we can eat Lu Tuitang, badger that previous time hunts for is also can only the tastiness, radically only then little few meat”

„Lancome, do not say.” The old person called granddaughter's name finally: „Our status hunt for slave, is the master makes us have the opportunity to live on this lands, does not give the words that the god the emperor presents tribute, we living the qualifications do not have, a bit faster manages! Let few variants help you.”

„Good.”

Young girl 100,000 are not glad grasps the hatchet to arrive by the deer corpse, was saying to me: „Does wild pig elder brother, I like eating Lu Toutang?”

I laugh in spite of trying not, when my Brother Cheng Shanzhu? However said: „Likes, my this person does not select food, can eat to the full was good, without many requests.”

„Snort.” She groans lightly, said: „Deer brain made soup to drink completely to you! Make suspect who your mouth mounts disgusting! Come, helping me cut off Lu Tou, then sends to honorable person there in the body.”

„Um.”

I have not met the hatchet, but draws out to do rapidly, a ray twinkle in the past, Lu Tou tumbled in the place, the blood already congealed, but does on a bloodstain not to have, turns over to the sheath rapidly, lifts up the deer corpse, said: „Does Lancome, where in the family, guide to me?”

„Good.”

Lancome turns around, with a smile is pulling the deer tail, said: „I refer to Lu Yo for you.”

After is a young young girl, is subject to changing moods, now actually probably knew well with me generally, in she turns around actually also to show the flavor that a young girl has grown into, the slender waist, the outstanding buttocks and milk-white bosom, all are the best quality goods, even the cheek of Lancome is also the great beautiful woman, even if wears the tight-fitting clothes of hunter unable to conceal her beauty originally.

My silently follows Lancome, on the track in village, hunts for the slaves to shoulder the game, some are many, some are few, several people are putting up a wild pig with the stick with joint forces, some are only tying up hares and several birds in the waist, does not need to think that a journey can only hunt to a person of hare affirmative is not only able to maintain the livelihood, on not to mention tribute.

Soon, light and spacious dwelling appears in a slightly at present, the front had several to hunt for the slave's tribute in the waiting, is one's turn our times, that wears the black clothed in strokes the beard lightly, a pair of pupil sweeps to sweep off in the chest buttocks of Lancome, said: „Lancome, you and income of grandfather journey is good, unexpectedly makes you hunt and kill a head good wild deer.”

Lancome self-confident is supporting small milk-white bosom, said: „In honorable person, this is natural, grandfather's archery ranks among the best in the village!”

„Ha Ha!”

In was examining game, suddenly the complexion got dark, said: „Lancome, why will the head of this wild deer disappear? We need a complete deer, like this roasts the standard to be good!”

Lancome puts in great inconvenience said: „I and grandfather two months had not tasted the meat taste, this time we this deer, did not have other any harvests, in the honorable person, you made us eat venison.”

In is sneering: „Eats the meat? You have forgotten, you just hunt for the slave, your masters are great Sir Yun Yu, do you want to present tribute not to have the deer of head to Sir Yun Yu?”

Lancome was suffering from injustice: „But but I forgot the meat taste quickly”

I said in side: „Sir, you show mercy, hunts and kills the deer in any case is not only then Lancome.”

„Who are you?”

In is showing the whites of the eyes to visit me: „Looked that your weapons are complete, should also be Xiuwu, how to appear here?”

Lancome is drawing my bracer hurriedly, said: „In the honorable person, wild pig elder brother is I and grandfather in travel who in the mountain found, he has just become lost, does not have what evil intention.”

In is smiling: „Is well-meant? You said that didn't have evil intention without the evil intention? Comes the human, gives me to take this boy, the father must think him well-meant really!”

After right person, two powerful and brave guys walked, in the hand is holding up the axe of murder.

I dept frown, lift the hand to draw out the butterfly sword, urging the valley to be mad, „buzz” a butterfly sword expressed a sharp sharp cry, the surroundings golden light lingered, an invisible pressure arrived in the surroundings, although I was not a god, but I had the strength of imperial day Frost passed on, the forge supernatural power pressure was very relaxed.

„You!”

In is startled slightly: „Are you god king?”

I did not speak, was default.

In just and two military people kneel immediately, the forehead knocks the sound on the ground, said: „Wang Zunqing forgives, we do not know really you are the god king, our we do not dare!”

I have not disclosed that said lightly: „Gets up, I came here matter everyone not to say, otherwise I let his state of mind Ju Mie! This deer, I shouldered, do not tell me to have any question . Moreover, in positive, the game that later can not levy the Lancome master grandson, cannot pick a quarrel in them, otherwise I killed certainly you.”

„Yes, yes! The villains act certainly accordingly!”

I shoulder the venison once more on shoulder, said to nearby young girl: „Lancome, walks goes back, today makes you eat deer bouillon, did not need to eat Lu Toutang again!”

Which Lancome knows the fear, cheers one to put my arms.

I am heavyhearted, the day boundary for me is only a fairyland, I sooner or later must walk, once I walked, some people feel embarrassed Lancome and grandfather again, what to do? Even if I am the god emperor, perhaps isn't able to control all that here has?

To work as a good person, is doomed to hobble entire life too!

Has an advertisement

Activity subject: Loses the fallen leaf: „My world anticipates your participation!”

Activity synopsis:

The web has constructed a virtual world system, allowing each player to participate in attacking a city effectively, the guild fight, the civilization development, the individual contact and other in the virtual social activities went to and can understand the different life in the game.

But loses the fallen leaf writing the web world is to eagerly anticipate thousands of readers enjoys able to move unhindered the pleasant sensation of virtual state!

Once they made our heart movement pursue all night, renovated the page under the announcement in front of the computer only for the chapter that first can see draws a charge fiery.

Now the sweet dumplings lose the fallen leaf build bridge to help you to interpret a dream with the web big god for you!

Regardless of you are the follower of frivolous student, wants to form a team to attack a city with the total defeat \; Perhaps wants to exchange with the [Zhan Long] short distance, or merely is the web novel author wants to obtain the big god to direct. Or in your heart has the fine bridge section to hope that shares with trillion netizens together.

Now takes up the cell phone downloading sweet dumplings to participate quickly!

So long as in world that in the web novel constructs, game system school Class or the world background duty captures can write a story centered on you. Can construct web persona, can the taking responsibility angle or the supporting role, can with losing the web novel lead of fallen leaf construction has occurring together, can not have, if the persona bright prominent has the opportunity to land to lose the fallen leaf work, shares with the netizen surely together.

Activities regulation:

1: Downloading debarkation „sweet dumplings creation” cell phone client side

2: Founds a work content to be related with the web novel in the sweet dumplings, or with losing the fallen leaf is related, the work label increases „loses fallen leaf” then.

Activity reward:

( 1 ) during the activities, will choose 10 lucky authors( maintains renewal active opportunity is bigger) the reward sweet dumplings official to have custom-made the present.

( 2 ) during the activities, to all participates in author to collect the issue: Is losing fallen leaf sweet dumplings work book review area to send out the question that you want to ask, and has the opportunity with losing the fallen leaf reaches the sweet dumplings star reception room together.

Note: The sweet dumplings reception room is the sweet dumplings exclusive column. The interview star writer, the excavation writes the bracelet unknown secret, told you to create the course back story.

( 3 ): „Loses fallen leaf” label top20 to construct the special demonstration

The schoolmate who wants to try to write can play ~

#1265: Flying upwards superior god!

Yun Qian is most powerhouses in seven big god emperors, once I defeat Yun Qian, means that I will show disdain for this potential surface, lets my heart fresh feeling generally, this so-called god, gods among obtains heterogeneous that clearly, the soldier slave and powder spirit, patrol hunting for and god to honor, the god king and god emperor, in their minds, the god emperor is unsurpassed to high existence, but I promoted 30% entire attributes almost to tie the god emperor, but I in every, promoted 150% entire attributes also as before am not the dark blue billows. The matches, the god of this potential surface has obviously how shortsightedly, probably Frost enters this potential surface words, to tall Shen.

„This”

Thunder and lightning are glittering around Yun Qian, his arm extends the flame, gathers the flame long blade in hand, the corners of the mouth shows to sneer, said: „Haven't you died unexpectedly?”

„Temple blesses, will not die.” My lazily smiling.

„That suffers to death!”

Yun Qian flushed suddenly, the hand medium baking temperature blade occupies a commanding position strikes, the speed is much faster, I do not have Cooldown to walk the position avoidance, can only lift the hand rapidly, does the sword continually without enough time remove, the shield of stars rapid spreads on the sword blade edge, „buzz” opens in the left arm front, „bang” a hit, fell 72% toughness, is really scary!

I no longer think anything, in works to wrap the purgatory ghost to raise the card, first promoted 10% striking power and 20% HP said again, otherwise could be killed by the second, and can also provide 50% thunder and lightning injuries to remit, this card specially in view of Yun Qian.

Really, after using up the purgatory ghost card, the killing injury that I place oneself in the thunder and lightning field of force every second of receive reduced 50%, was not again fatal, but cannot be negligent as before, [Seven Stars Teleportation] position [Soul Army] [Azure Dragon Crossbow] release together, Ancient Heavenly Tiger was also summoned, You Yi in the one side, actually could not find the opportunity of starting, the war of god emperor, as if the pet of Demon Harvest step was unable to meddle.

Adopts the tour to fight the tactic as before, mainly outputs the method is [Great Realm of Desolation], [Azure Dragon Crossbow] and [Seven Star Fragment Slash], uses fatally the escape position avoids Yun Qian strikes, then touches to -type the way output rides the wind to cut, [Strength of a Thousand Men], therefore scene basically I completely am inferior, was being pursued killing by the god emperor, only has after my riding the wind cut, [Strength of a Thousand Men] CD well will contact close combat, this can assure my own security, before HP of god emperor was lower than 50% should better do not hand over too many skills, at least the eternal boundaries and domain of two big skill god cannot. The junction, otherwise the behind 50% blood will make me die once more.

When a master, must learn to plan carefully.

These time smooth surpasses my expectation, the purgatory ghost was good the effect of card, restrains Lei Xi who Yun Qian has most excelled at to attack the injury completely, but the issue came at this time, near 50 minutes of time I will say that shallow HP consumes to 50%, but purgatory ghost persistent Cooldown merely 120 minutes of card, if the card effect lost BOSS actually not dead, that following died approximately on was I!

Speeds up outputting!

Cooldown every little bit is passing, when Yun Qian 40% HP, opened another strong fire is the crowd kills the skill, my HP started unable to stand firm, but has not used skill, stood firm furiously, when Yun Qian HP remaining 35%, started frequent use one to be called „ice spin” the attack effect, can freeze 0.5 second the human, broke the skill directly, he was too intelligent, after I will leave to ride the wind to cut each time at least will break to exceed 10 times, some attacked.

Finally, after the continual two knocking of god emperor, my HP emptied instantaneously!

Death!

Immediately chooses overlord rebirth resurrecting, but system System Notification I, in 10 seconds will also be transmitted!

In pulls out to wrap hurriedly two I Ching pill, swallows together!

„Brushes!”

The golden light flows swiftly to fall together, rose 235 levels, and obtained 30% entire attribute addition effects, long sword one cold, fought with all might with the god emperor once more in the same place, this time had the energy to be many.

Yun Qian the attack is continuous, has suddenly to strike continuously time can scare to death the human simply, is good also frequently appears because of my Dinghai effect, several savior, restored 50% HP too to be simply easy-to-use.

Cooldown every little bit passing, when Yun Qian 20% HP, attack even more bone-chilling cold, animal general fiercely attacking, the [Soul Army] minefield pattern, the hot axe and Saint cut three big skill almost bang to kill together on me, but boundary of large-scale skill my eternal compelling, the output, has been entangling the BOSS chaotic dance long sword furiously.

„Bang bang bang”

Bone-chilling cold sword air/Qi spatter in all directions on the summit, carries over the snows of innumerable scattering, simultaneously I also noticed that in the cave of distant place a ray shoots up to the sky, Lancome flew upwards successfully, she became a god Venerable, when she trod the cave, I the look one order her to go back immediately severely, even if became the fight that the god Venerable here is not she can participate, was good is also obedient because of Lancome, in the obedient returning cave waited for my fight result.

When HP of god emperor remaining 10%, the purgatory ghost the Cooldown also only also remaining 12 minutes of card, my heartbeat soon stopped, this showdown continued Cooldown to be too long, already for nearly 100 minutes, moreover killed by my attack output as before was so long, this god emperor strong? On the words of HP quantity, compared favorably with any Hybrid Demon king sufficiently, even can compare favorably with Stella this prehistoric giant beast!

The domain of god, starts! Meets Cooldown of eternal boundary, otherwise could not block.

God emperor Yun Qian in roaring, but own HP actually little was worn down up by me, when I start the [Thundering Heavens] + Longteng nine days kill together, this god emperor thoroughly is enraged, brandishes the flame long blade to divide to chop the shield of my stars, while the anger exclaimed: „Is impossible! Is impossible, you are only a trivial mortal, you are only ants, how this emperor will die in your hands, this is absolutely impossible, damn, I must kill you, I must dismember a body you!”

What a pity, said the ruthless words everybody metropolis.

The death of god emperor was imminent, but my heart also mentioned the throat, when Yun Qian HP 2%, my purgatory ghost the card Cooldown also only remaining 1 minutes 57 seconds, NND, so long as the ghost remits the effect to disappear the 50% thunder and lightning of card, the surrounding [Soul Army] minefield pattern can the instantaneous second kill me, if BOSS, when 1% blood have killed me, my definitely meeting wants dead.

In fact the destiny goddess quite cares for me actually.

My final strikes is rides the wind to cut, 15 times cut struck strongly finally to the five to strike 2 times to leave fatally has struck, 1 time struck except for Superior, one time left the 4 times of attacks of butterfly sword, this set of output directly has polished directly god emperor Yun Qian final 1% HP, almost same Cooldown, the purgatory ghost attached Cooldown card in addition instantaneously by the detachment!

Day! Succeeded!

Drops down in the god emperor, body changes into dust dissipations time, I also all of a sudden knee down, the mental effort of whole person almost soon overdrew, this BOSS was in BOSS that I massacred hardest to deal with one, most made me exhaust the skills.

In the cave, the Lancome rapid flight comes, one falls down in my arms, bursts into tears with a smile: „Wild pig elder brother, Elder brother, you have massacred god emperor Yun Qian finally, good, good, you are the new god emperor!”

I am also happy, the left hand embraced the slender waist of Lancome, the right hand has been picking up Yun Qian the godship, inside this glittering and translucent carving godship was glittering the thunder and lightning, the incorruptible and sacred aura, but the surrounding was lingering the light flame, grasped warm feelings in the control, when at this time didn't fly upwards also treats?

Builds up directly, immediately the godship changes into golden light to seep my body, is having the incomparably vigorous strength, next quarter, a system ting reverberation in the sky of entire server

„Bites!”

System announcement: Congratulates the player 【Xiao Yao Zi Zai】( China) flies upwards successfully is 【Superior god】( Thunder and lightning &\; incorruptible &\; flame &\; sacred), is 5 th flies upwards for the player of god, obtains the reward: Level + 2, charm value + 80, gold coins several + 150000, after flying upwards, the entire hideaway attribute large scale promotion, the strength growth promotes 150%, Stamina growth to promote 100%, Agility growth to promote 80%, Magic growth to promote 60%, all skills break through 20 levels, practices skilled to promote to the god step 7 levels high!

Instantaneous 237 levels, and after flying upwards, the attribute also had very big change, before every 10 strengths can make me promote 7-10 points attacks, now can actually promote 17.5-25 points for me the striking power, but the Stamina value direction, my Dragon Rider is 1 Stamina value promotes 8 HP Class, now turns has promoted 16 points, equipment fixed addition has not changed, but the promotion in additional aspect had very obvious promotion, my equipment + attribute added that on having 38000 + strengths, overlord coverall each added 4000-5000 strengths to be possible. It is not false, the present foundation striking power was the real full house

【Xiao Yao Zi Zai】( Town day Dragon Rider)

Level: 237

Attack: 110055-144570

Defense: 47732

Life: 845120

Magic: 128492

Charm value: 2303

CBN fights the net rank: 2

Title: Broken cauldron male

God level: Superior god

Striking power thorough explosive table, because the overlord coverall main attack attribute adds in the strength value, but is not in the striking power, each equipment overlord special effect , to promote 5000 strengths, therefore after flying upwards , to promote the strength to grow, this flies upwards regarding the player, I was the biggest beneficiary, the foundation striking power already thousand +, after the addition, nearly was simply invincible, even I thought before Fang Ge Que flew upwards, once after by my near body, can a sword broken shield, a sword murder?

Thinks carefully that this is very likely!

After system System Notification I 120 minutes, will be left by the automatic transmission, is not good, must bring Lancome to leave here in 120 minutes, she extremely elegantly, is the god Venerable, in this god emperor day boundary of able to move unhindered looks like beautiful Yangyang falls in the ash wolves simply is too same.

But, where re-enters the entrance of boundary?

Time that I transmit appears in directly airborne, this seeks?

Thinks of here, then closes the eye, the intent sea lets loose, in flash mind „buzz”, had a scare me, after flying upwards superior god, I the intent sea in game extend dozens li (0.5km) unexpectedly instantaneously, the strength in space surge to see clearly without doubt, in not the far place, potential surface crack, so long as the strength urged to send can open.

Previous god emperor Yun Qian as if forcefully opens the crack with this means that but likely is not my such, Benben must drill the volcano and drill ditch sole, tastes completely the misery.

„Lancome, we walked.”

Grasps Lancome, this time did not need thousand frost wings to fly, jumped, the speed of light has fired into the space crack of distant place, distant rumbled a fist, „bang”, the supernatural power of superior god concentrated on the fist wind has formed a highly regarded shock-wave, has ripped open a potential surface opening directly, jumped to enter, at present „whish” one bright, appeared in the boundary!

#1271: The war of revenge

The world forbids today of land mine, Wang Ze Cheng lays down the destructive land mine in the surroundings of villa unexpectedly, is this how rash? However, since he breeds to install the matter of person to be able continually to meddle the chief instigator, that was also nothing unusual.

This is an ejection land mine, so long as I will lift the foot to spring the explosion.

„Was boss, how motionless?” The night vision aiming of Xing Lie correct use sniper's rifle visits me.

„All right.”

My light [say / way], drinks afterward lowly, Yang Yan the roaring flame proliferates the whole body immediately, formed flame remnant Armor to protect me, lifts under that moment of starting to transmit „” an explosion, the huge impact made me fall to fly with the sword, both legs numb, under hot Armor protected oneself not to have what important matter.

The whereabouts has exposed, that has nothing to worry that jumps, but directly soars the villa group, but Xing Lie in consternation said in communication: „Your you stepped on to the land mine!”

„All right, reported my concrete Wang Ze Cheng in the position!”

„Main building 3, the room by west, Wang Ze Cheng, a woman, as if a little have not looked familiar, probably is that smoke in game locks the love affair!”

„How to do the same place?”

I somewhat wonder, but periphery already head lamp headlamp full, this villa group nearby according to well-illuminated, here guard had been alarmed completely!

„Some people sneak attack, hurry up!”

In the villa exudes the sounds of people, dozens people raised the [Assault] (spear|gun) to clash, simply was a nest of thieves, what person had, what weapon had!

I draw out the pistol, sprints, while burst, almost (spear|gun) solution these people, but surrounding full is the crowded bullet, avoids again is unable to avoid completely, the good bullet hits on Yang Yanhua the armor spatters in all directions the ball to start in abundance, only consumption was real of my within the body is mad, the fever were less, this was certain.

„Whiz!”

A rocket launcher brings the thick smoke to fly, my hurried bends down, it almost pasted my sending tree top to fly, „bang” behind was blasting out, the flame soared to the heavens, my goodness, this sound was really makes suffices in a big way!

„Puff puff”

Long-distance points shoot down on this group of hoodlums, 11 strike to massacre, is the reenforcement of Xing Lie, as if also incessantly Xing Lie, should be several other snipers also together helps.

„Boss, I mass-criticized the main building with track directly, how is it?” The axe said in communication.

I shake the head hurriedly: „No, Xu Yue also in inside, she is just a stupid woman, is insufficient to want her dead, moreover this time we can find the Wang Ze Cheng crime evidence to be best!”

„Yes, needs to expedite reenforces the time, although said that I have brought the heavy weapon of base completely, entire third engineer!”

„”

The soldiers who really I lead are one group of lunatics.

The butterfly sword under the moonlight flood the fearful gloss, I am raising the sword hilt, the sword blade edge is hanging down, directly soars one group of people to go, Xing Lie and the others bullets as if steadily eye general clears the way for me, the hoodlum who will hold a gun strikes to massacre, but these people as if also understood a matter, the bullet and land mine attacked to me invalid, this was Yang Yan the scala media strength.

„Tears into shreds him!”

In the villa hears one to whoosh, 9 dragon blood soldiers flushed together.

I deeply inspire, the illness drew back several steps suddenly, the right hand holds up the butterfly sword, the left hand is actually searching in the waist, works on an anti-tank grenade the link to throw on draw, how this group of dragon blood soldiers think that the solemn Yang Yan powerhouse will do this set, immediately was erupted directly in the crowd by the anti-tank grenade, „” an explosion, although was insufficient to be killed violently is also actually blown by the shock-wave leans this way and that.

The opportunity came!

Explodes the thick smoke has not dissipated time I overran, the butterfly sword in a flash, the consecutively three swords, airborne then flew three heads, solved three instantaneously, lifted to start to trample fiercely, on tip of the toe the strength of thick Yang Yan, kicked to explode the head of fourth dragon blood soldier directly, but on shoulder suddenly one tight, sharp claws of dragon blood soldier, but there is a hot Armor guard, could not injure me, instead by Yang Yanjia hot the pitiful yell, turned around is a sword, shut off around the middle.

Also the remaining four dragon blood soldiers, almost together threw.

My both hands grasped the sword, the butterfly are already burnt down a handle flame sharp sword by Yang Yan, but absolutely did not have the meaning of melting, red, but, a sword did not puncture to go suddenly, punctured thoroughly a head of dragon blood soldier, a body spin, the both arms caught up suddenly, the butterfly sword was making a circular arc same place, was two heads flies, the last dragon blood soldier stood there, unexpectedly felt the fear, does not dare to go forward.

„Puff!”

A distant place bullet has shot, is accurate, shot through his eye directly, the nano ball was unable to penetrate his scale, but the hit eye and oral cavity can explode the head, Xing Lie the marksmanship also was really.

I said in communication: „I went upstairs, you wipe out all glasses, maintains the field of vision, momentarily reenforcement!”

„Good!”

An arrow step enters the villa, found the staircase to overrun, simultaneously outside gunshots, are combining the glass shatter sound, this time thinks that Wang Ze Cheng has not thought I can come to destroy Huanglong.

Also the bodyguards of several holding a gun are blocking along the way the way as before, but how can block [Vanguard] of butterfly, complete cutting to pieces of sword sword!

„Bang!”

The numerous foot, trampled the front door of western room, that trampled to turn into the smashing in my violent force immediately, in the dust, Wang Ze Cheng has worn a western-style clothing, but nearby Xu Yue actually as before wore the night clothes . Moreover, a middle-aged person of wear black T-shirt held the arm to stand there, vision ice-cold visits me: „Are you Li Xiao Yao?”

„Who are you?” I asked lightly.

„Wang De, practices in Mt. Zhongnanshan.”

„Makes way, do not keep off me.”

„I, if doesn't let?”

„That dies.”

„Ha Ha” Wang De sends out to laugh, said: „I heard that you are Yang Yan, but how your age so possibly is Yang Yan, thinks that is also generation of the gaining fame by deceiving people, comes, actually making the grandfather experience a Xiayang flame the strength how!”

When I go upstairs received the hot Armor guard, enters the time strength of this room is reducing naturally to lowest, this can save is mad, because I need time can erupt hot Armor to protect oneself instantaneously with the strongest Yang Yan strength, Wang De of this Royal Air peak too was probably big with my disparity, unexpectedly cannot see clearly my strength completely, alternatively, I, when outside strikes kills the dragon blood soldier, strength full, if he opens the intent sea, this induction obtains to?

„Brushes!”

Moves sideways, my speed has gone far beyond Wang De, above the left fist full is the roaring flame, „puff passed” one to hit thoroughly his chest directly, the blood has spattered in all directions, Royal Air peak, was a round matter.

„”

Wang De opens the mouth, the blood is flowing crazily, opens the eye, as if not believe all that at present sees, but he truly died, this jumped over the fate of two-level challenge.

If I currently initially the Ouyang Chuan strength, perhaps Wang De also had a slim chance of survival, but my present strength absolutely by far Ouyang Chuan, especially when Shen Bing died in the line of duty, my cavity anger appears, this is no different is courting death, to take revenge for her and Dong Cheng Lei, I can not work as the police, will I also care kill one person?

„!”

A scream, Xu Yue looks that Wang De's corpse drops down slowly, afterward visits me, in the vision has been full of the fear: „Li Xiao Yao, your you killed people! Your this murderer!”

I laugh in spite of trying not, said: „Xu Yue, outside has more than one rail gun to aim here, momentarily can mass-criticize the even this villa, you know why I don't make them open fire? Because of you here, you are innocent, immediately get lost, quick!”

Wang Ze Cheng actually Ha Ha smiling: „Li Xiao Yao, you may really be too ruthless.”

„Has you to suppress?” I am nipping the steel tooth.

„Yes, what you said is that attractive young policewoman? Really has been a pity, did an inside job in [Thousand Burial] was so long, went to close Pei Ying that idiot desirably, moreover was so attractive, the both legs exploded did not have, was really a pity, what a pity”

Wang Ze Cheng nearly in fierce is laughing, I near the video establishment photography with ear all these, the direct transmission returned to the headquarters, at least this could be the ironclad proof?

„Rustle”

The body of Wang Ze Cheng is having transformation, flame scales appear on his face, the nape of the neck, chest and arm, in an instant he also has become the dragon blood soldier such monster, Xu Yue frightens screams one, compared with appearance that my hot Armor protects oneself, Wang Ze Cheng now is perhaps scarier, completely is a monster.

Dingy flushed from the front door, Xu Yue ran, I said in communication: „Xu Yuetao exited, sends for aiding her, do not injure accidentally.”

Laughing that Wang Ze Cheng cannot bear, saliva star spattered in all directions, the hand pointed at me saying: „Li Xiao Yao Li Xiao Yao, when do you want the womanly compassion to? This Xu Yue is worth protecting, she was just a father plays greasily **, what's wrong, do you also want to rest her? Doesn't the result that your this heroes, most like rest the woman who oneself have protected?”

I have not spoken, shouted , the butterfly sword has rumbled!

My speed above him, Wang Ze Cheng is unable to move aside absolutely, but is not unexpectedly startled, suddenly raises the arm, roaring flame condense on the arm, unexpectedly completed has protected oneself the same defensive system with my hot Armor, was this?!

„!”

A bang, strength shock-wave breaks nearby window glass all, I raise the long sword to draw back several steps continually, Wang Ze Cheng is more miserable, on the arm splutters blood, stumbles on the wall, the impact is too big, the entire wall has produced the crack.

His slowly crawls from the ground, saying with a smile of glorious defeat: „Faces up to the technical the strength, Li Xiao Yao, you thought that you did step into Yang Yan on the unmatched in the world? It is not, I collect your cell and DNA, studies your DNA sudden change and arrangement rule, I can also become Yang Yan the powerhouse, moreover is the resiliency by far your Yang Yan powerhouse . Moreover, I can make many S levels to breed installing, you felt that was afraid?”

I do not utter a word, unites the strength of whole body in the sound of long sword, an arrow step + chops to cut!

„!”

Wang Ze Cheng miserable howling, an entire left arm uneven velamen I have chopped, the disgusting blood spatters in all directions everywhere is, he as if insane generally, laughs saying: „You how me, you forever how me.”

Saying, his one was jumping to break the window, crawled following the wall.

I also pursued, several arrow steps arrived at the roof, but does not see the Wang Ze Cheng trace, actually discovered that several intense light beams condense on oneself, is the ray of armed helicopter.

„Boss!” Xing Lie said anxiously: „They have the armed helicopter, be careful, will the rebel that altogether three armed helicopters, have not registered, mother, how this group of people do these?”

My hurried luck, the intensity promotion that hot Armor protects oneself to highest, at the same time loudly shouted to clear the way: „Axe, mass-criticizes these helicopters with the track, should not be worried to injure me!”

„Yes, immediately calibrates!”

But before the axe calibrates, the airborne flames flushed, I sink immediately at heart, is the missile, the day, the instantaneous 6 missiles have locked me!

Clenches teeth, shouts angrily a frontage to withstand these injuries!

„Bang bang bang!”

A flame, almost anything is unable to see clearly, the continuous at least several miniature missiles explode around me, the body of whole person as if must be torn into shreds general.

#1282: Continues to evolve!

Beside abatement Long Xiangkui, Bai Qi appeared quite mean-spirited, moreover only blew out a handle silver sword, 240 levels of Demon Harvest pointed weapons, since the serial number of Demon Harvest broke through 9999 after two months ago, own value in starting to depreciate unceasingly, must miss the big scale compared with a star magical instrument and inferior magical instrument, although wanted to be stronger than the stall goods, but ended to explode equipment of Demon Harvest in the auction room is actually a big pile.

Demon Harvest, sur- two day plume, the fourth BOSS knock rating simply is pitiful.

However, my vision stays in that tea fragrance and color skill book, puts out a hand to grasp, the arm shakes slightly, the introduction of books reappears in the nighttime sky, several female were immediately astonished has opened the small mouth, no one has thought that unexpectedly most beckoning the skill book on Bai Qi exploding, this time has made up for the loss of equipment knock rating completely

【Sword broken landscape】( star territory military Secret Art ★★★★): Launches the sword intent attack, kills to formation sword air/Qi within front 120 yards, sword intent such as the landscape picture scroll is vast, after 1.5 seconds , the picture scroll disintegration, creates own striking power 150% attack killing, cools the Cooldown 60 seconds, the study consumes 50 charm values, needs the Level 240 levels, needs Class: The entire soldiers are Class.

Lin Wan Er shallow faint smile: „Congratulates our family pig head, this time has not attained any equipment, but has at least attained a skill book of star territory rank, looks like the very strong appearance!”

I nod: „Um, the lethality and kill zone compared with [Seven Star Fragment Slash] much, simply be the group fight the sharp weapon, good skill!”

Saying, was lifting the hand to wield, the skill book vanished in the palm, has studied successfully, in my skill fence also naturally left a skill, was the design of sword and picture scroll overlap, looked like with the shield of same radiance stars, was at heart feeling pleased, at present should I be only simultaneously have two star territory rank skills players? The shield and sword broken landscape stars, defends attacks, supplementary insufficiency!

The skill studies successfully, looked for an open area, I lift the right hand suddenly, immediately a vigorous strength emerges the right arm to concentrate on crazily fiercely in the butterfly sword, the long sword ray rises sharply, wields suddenly, „whish” golden light clears the way, in 120 code lengths, in a width at least 20 yards range unfolds rapidly together the picture scroll, the mountain range, river, beautiful woman and other present, after 1.5 seconds , the picture disintegration, changes into ice edges and rocks to kill suddenly in the open area, in an instant has formed a piece of gully in confusion on this road, unexpectedly has certain destructive power to the map, this skill blockhouse!

„Was good, other was beautiful.”

Lin Wan Er eats a hand that smiles, in the palm three cards, said with a smile: „The Bai Qi star card, received.”

„Um.”

I have swept one, the Bai Qi star card seemed to be overbearing

【Star card &\;@ Bai Qi】 × 3: Promotes 150% striking power with 40% Military Control effects( team defensive power + 80%) , to continue for 120 minutes!

120 minutes of in addition holds the team attribute, such star card absolutely is the treasure of valuable non- city, after all major Guild challenge ultra god level BOSS time earnestly seeking degree to this type of card quite exaggerates, these preliminary star cards that in the market condition circulates can only promote many 10% Military Control effects, promoting the team 20% defensive powers to be extraordinary, but these 3 Bai Qi star cards promoted user own 150% attacks and team 80% defensive powers unexpectedly, kills not two choices that BOSS and country fought simply!

Receiving, this type of card is not needing to consider that has sold, we can serve a need.

Considered that Lin Wan Er, Dong Cheng Yue and Dancing Forest work as the possibility of team leader not to be high, therefore divided a Bai Qi star card to give Wan Er, other two I was receiving, in own manpower, when the time comes received is also a person on one's own side who in any case moistened.

Receives the good card, I said: „Was good, should we embark next? Also does not know that the beginning imperial tomb fifth also has anything, perhaps was the beginning emperor is greeting us directly.”

Dong Cheng Yue said with a smile: „His old bones, we can definitely be him in any case.”

„Look”

I am raising the long sword, gradually moved toward five along stone steps, four female also cautiously followed, arrived at 50% me to open the god shape, cannot be negligent absolutely, no one knows that beginning imperial tomb five also had anything.

„Rustle”

Fights the boots to tread when the underground five grounds, I had a scare by the surrounding situation, five vast that is far from us imagining, even is only one fine and space not big tomb chamber, this is one is similar existence in main hall, probably the beginning emperor main hall according to Xianyang constructs, on the giant stone column the pelycosauria surrounds, stern incomparable, but does not have any guard, in extreme of main hall, is not the emperor place, what replaces it is a giant coffin.

„The coffin of Qin Shi Huang” Darling Duck somewhat is slightly small excitedly, after all the Qin Shi Huang mausoleum until now where is a riddle, moreover reality also nobody found the inner and outer coffin of beginning emperor, although now in game, but is unavoidable excitedly.

I am raising butterfly sword close inner and outer coffin step by step, is at heart getting more and more excited, some not good premonitions, will Qin Shi Huang always jump to give me to come one set of nine cloudy bones of the dead fingernails from the inner and outer coffin?

Lin Wan Er is following close on me, is drawing my cloak, on the beautiful cheek full is anxious, but wants to have a look in the inner and outer coffin to have Qin Shi Huang, appearance in a dilemma lovably comedy.

The cold wind whiz whiz, entire beginning imperial tomb five are silent, dies the general tranquility.

My approaching inner and outer coffin step by step, lifts the hand to move on the cover of inner and outer coffin, immediately a biting cold chill in the air transmits, what in this coffin thinks is what? It is not good, definitely has matter to occur!

Tranquil is almost oppressing to result when in this type the human suffocates, suddenly behind Dong Cheng Yue came one: „Brother Xiao Yao, holds coffin autopsy”

„Puff”

I and Lin Wan Er have smiled together, the atmosphere also suddenly reverses.

„”

The coffin covers rubs the voice of coffin to be very grating slowly, I turn down half the coffin lid, does not have first Cooldown to look that in has anything, Wan Er is holding my arm, brave is extending the tall snow white nape of the neck, looked in the coffin, afterward spits the tongue.

„What's wrong?”

„Anything does not have.”

„?”

I look down suddenly, actually had a scare, should lie down the place of beginning emperor corpse not to have a thing in the world, only then quilt of a rotten brocade pillow and shop bottom of coffin, almost rotted completely, thick decayed smell fills the air in the surroundings.

„Can't?”

I was utterly confused, our time comes the beginning imperial tomb to seek to pass on the country imperial jade seal, but the corpse of beginning emperor here, where will not pass on the country imperial jade seal, became the riddle?

Sees my disappointed appearance, Lin Wan Er probably does not feel better, puts out a hand to cover the coffin shoves open completely!

„Buzz!”

A ray from the end place of coffin flood, I and Wan Er almost simultaneously looked at the past, saw together the imperial jade seal impressively, I held cautiously, saw only on the imperial jade seal truly to carve „is having a mandate from heaven, not only long-lived Yongchang” . Moreover the angle of imperial jade seal had the breakage, the part that with golden patching, that should be Wang Mang usurped the throne the queen mother gets angry to move, afterward imperial jade seal wandering about destitute folk, and was found to return here by the later generation guard of Qin Shi Huang, then, these guards? Passing away up? Joins became part of terracotta warrior, moreover which did Qin Shi Huang go? It is not really good to explain.

Does not manage, passes on country imperial jade seal to succeed in obtaining!

„Was this map this brushes?” Dong Cheng Yue asked with a smile.

I nod: „Um, had finished, although has not attained good equipment, but the empirical value is very plentiful, the preparation returns to the city!”

„Oh.”

Searches again, not having perquisite may fish, returns to the city!

Also at this moment, suddenly a ting reverberation above the Tian Ling Empire sky

„Bites!”

System System Notification: Fellow players please note, situated in East China Sea Coordinate ( 38181,17262 ) map 【Beginning imperial tomb】 The official present world, the beginning imperial tomb altogether has 4, each has BOSS, each BOSS refresh cycle is 72 hours, the refresh cycle of antiquity warrior level monster was 60 minutes!

The map opened officially, will certainly become the stretch of land that must fight for of players.

I said silently: „Several BOSS death Cooldown have you remembered?”

Lin Wan Er carefully like dust: „Um, I, have not thought that will apply.”

I show a faint smile: „That did not have what issue, let Li Mu or Fox leads a number of [Zhan Long] brothers to pass, one hour small renovated strangely one time, practiced the level is good, remembered the BOSS refresh cycle, hundred people roll to kill BOSS people should not be difficult.”

„Knows that arranges immediately.”

„OK, I made the arms upgrade the matter.”

„Online so is continuously long, a bit faster offline eats the thing to sleep.”

„Knows.”

However the material has gotten ready, at this time made my offline eat meal is impossible, after the good and evil must the butterfly promoted, be able offline!

Has a look at the good friend to list, in the morning 10 o'clock, Fox and Nangong spirit online, therefore sends the news immediately, the Fan Shu City building up Fangli gathers.

When I rush, Fox arrived, in the hand is holding one pile of stage props, said with a smile: „200 ten thousand years of profound irons and 3 19 steps built the atlas to prepare readily, did your biography country imperial jade seal take?”

„Naturally, how will otherwise the system clear the beginning imperial tomb map?”

„Hey, I know that this map definitely is you in the lane, otherwise not that big sound.”

At this time, Nangong progressed to come, to stand up from failure spirit to discontinue, said with a smile: „Does Brother Guildmaster, handle?”

„Um.”

I pulled out passed on the country imperial jade seal, the raw material that in addition Fox got so far as added on the butterfly sword one and gives Nangong to work.

„Did I start?”

„Good!”

Nangong starts to come spirit busily, first builds up big pile of ten thousand years of profound irons of the smelting, the iron thick liquid tumbles to seethe with excitement in the stove, then used has built the atlas, afterward posted the butterfly sword, immediately the long sword wrapped the thick ray to hang above the stove, the unceasing buying in atlas and strength of ten thousand years of profound iron, at this time, Nangong took out spirit passed on the country imperial jade seal, put in the palm, patted suddenly broken!

„Bang!”

This treasure changes into the powder pink / white to fall into the stove in abundance, fuses in the iron thick liquid of ten thousand years of profound iron together, can see that the tyrant soul of antiquity king in hum was miserably howling.

#1321: Fights the dark blue billows

The rumor howls in the ear, after entering the northern boundary , is not peaceful, I have massacred the sword spirit cavalry soldier of several batch of air patrols all the way, such alert degree by far in the past, does not need to want certainly to enter the Hybrid Demon territory to be related with Frost, child Shu and the others, only what now needs to determine is their exact location.

The bird's eye view earth, the front ascends bunch of mist and dust, as if had gone through the war for a long time, this is a small Hybrid Demon fort, in the fort everywhere is the corpses, majority is Hybrid Demon , the part is humanity, these humanity wear the mail-armor and helmet, the side residual break pointed weapons are Dragon’s den are specially-made, the Dragon’s den armed soldiers encountered here have fought!

I from the sky circle for one week, all around has a look, has not seen the corpse of big dragon, luckily, the Dragon Rider gentleman has not had any casualties here, wants to come Frost, child, Seurre and others to have NPC of god level strength not to make the Dragon Rider gentleman die in battle easily.

Suddenly, sees a form of limping in the corner, is one is dragging to entrain the blood demon of Dragon’s den armed soldier corpse, 6 levels of Hybrid Demon, use the corpse of humanity as the food, thinks that looks for food here.

I dive rapidly, the numerous foot tramples in its abdomen, stumbles its dozen in the city wall, goes forward a foot to step its chest, the butterfly sword arrives on the nape of the neck, shouted to clear the way lowly: „The words that does not want dead answered me an issue!”

He frightens trembles, already saw my body week the god shape corona, knows that I am a powerhouse of god level, nods to say again and again: „Chivalrous person you asked at will that I know say all, do not kill me, do not kill me!”

I asked: „Was the cold uncultivated land Dragon’s den regiment has attacked here?”

„Yes! They kill and burn to plunder, killed off my brothers completely.”

„Few idle talk, now which do they go?”

„Probably is” his eyeball one round, said: „Probably is”

My direct right hand catches up, a small section of butterfly pricks in his body stiffly, I sneer saying: „You spoke are best to pay attention to a point, otherwise this sword got down you definitely dead!”

„I know! I know!” He is almost calling out loudly: „They went to the scarlet mountain range, the dark blue billows Sir was summoning all Shen from purgatory, the Dragon’s den people goes to the scarlet mountain range!”

I show a faint smile, he visits me immediately anxiously: „You had said does not kill my!”

I also smiled: „I truly do not want to kill you, but keeps here you, you will swallow the corpses of these dying in battle, they are the brave warriors of humanity, should not by like this treatment, therefore, I must kill you!”

Was saying sword blade edge delivers, passes the nape of the neck, carries over over a million injury digit, comes one set of skill again, this blood demon tilted the head to hang immediately.

Cooldown is urgent, cannot allow to delay, immediately locks the scarlet mountain range the direction, full speed flight!

Near 20 minutes of full speed flights, the scarlet mountain range has heaved in sight by far, the mountain range surrounding even can see wreckage of all trades Long Jing artillery, in the ground full is the corpse of Hybrid Demon and humanity, here has certainly experienced a brutal fight, after I fall to the ground saw Kozayama neat cleft in two, this certainly is the Frost behavior, under the attack of sword air/Qi, the corpse of two ancient times giant beast lay down there, the wound was neat, was divided into two.

The blood of giant beast is still flowing, obviously the fight ended is not quite long.

I jump hurriedly , to continue to pursue the line.

All the way almost everywhere is the battlefields, quick, I saw the corpse of first Dragon Rider gentleman and big dragon, is a fire Dragon Rider gentleman, his big dragon nape of the neck place was divided a deep wound, the entire head was almost unloaded, but the chest of Dragon Rider gentleman was penetrated a Dadong, who god knows is can have such skill, punctures the body of Dragon Rider gentleman all of a sudden, can this need the big strange strength?

Continues to fly forward, quick one after another sees the Dragon Rider corpse, one after another, about 50 Dragon Rider gentlemen have offered the life here, Hybrid Demon that however died are more, dense and numerous piece.

Wait / Etc.!

Above the earth is lying down a monster, is a whole body is throwing over the soldier of lava, the body is very huge, about three meters high, grandiose incomparable, the chest has covered entirely the sword and trace of bow arrow, should fight randomly is killed, the mortal wound is the dog marks of nape of the neck place, that is the damage that the dragon claw causes, should be child Queen Shu the behavior.

Then this lava soldier should be the dark blue billows one of the ten devils from the purgatory summoning? By his corpse, altogether the corpses of several Dragon Rider gentlemen, the price to kill him paying were too many are too many.

Walks quickly, fight distance here is not far!

My low-altitude flying goes rapidly, cannot be too free, if possible I will choose the sneak attack, will kill the opposite party main action, after all the sneak attack will be quite more sane, because this will be the best self-preservation way.

„Bang!”

Long-distance transmits a startled day the bellow, the entire mountain range as if has blasted out generally, is away from me approximately inside and outside three, that hill top spatters in all directions crushed stones, the sword air/Qi shoots up to the sky, is having stars strengths, that is Frost is fighting!

However, above the earth is dense a light black energy, that is the dark energy, dark blue billows also.

Combat that airborne starts to circle shadows, the Dragon Rider gentleman gone all out.

Cannot wait, now goes!

„Clang!”

Draws out the butterfly sword rapidly, my full speed flight goes, after crossing the mountain peak, the present fight scene has only been able with stirring to describe

The Frost whole body covers entirely the star territory supernatural power, in the hand holds up the energy shield to resist fiercely attacking of dark blue billows, dark energies wreak havoc in the surroundings, corrodes her body unceasingly, but not far away, in the ground dense and numerous full are the corpse of big dragon and Dragon Rider gentleman, child Queen Shu changed into the red dragon flour shape, whooshes to prey in the working from before light until after dark color lava soldier together, Long Claw brandishes to bring together the lava fragment each time, but the defense of lava soldier was too high, Axe times falling in their hand on the dragon scale of child Shu's, chop the scale breakage and blood to spatter in all directions straight, this. The fight scene was too frigid.

Seurre dances in the air in airborne, actually encounters two to wave sharp claws chasing down of devil, can only draw out the waist dagger to come to square to keep off the attack, and some standards could not block, the dark blue billows this time the lava soldiers who summoned from the purgatory are the strength of king level, the child Shu Queen this Long Shen strength also can only select two only.

Had not discovered the sound that Aodiliya, does not know which she went.

In the ground, large quantities of Dragon’s den armed soldier and Hybrid Demon army fights with all might in the same place, here is a scarlet mountain range Oyamadani, but also turned into the human purgatory, had the massive people dead in battle every second.

Must grasp Cooldown, when otherwise Sif, Qin Ge and other kings ran away, here could not resist.

Lava soldier strength of dark blue billows summon is very strong, is equal to the king, but understands at a glance the intelligence quotient to be not much, is unable to place on a par with Sif, qin song these genuine king levels, must catch up before they come back ends here fight!

First helps child Queen Shu, she is here beside most powerhouse except Frost!

„Bang!”

Fights the boots to erupt in the air to attack together, overrunning of quickest speed, with the camp attacking mode, flies high to release eternal boundary skill, the people striking power promotes 50%, defensive powers to promote 150%, restores 20% HP every second, but child Shu and other NPC have not withstood this to restore the effect obviously completely, probably restores 2% HP every second, is good, better than nothing!

The double sword is together uneven the sheath, I settle on wound between the lava soldier napes of the neck, the meteor bang pounds!

„” The crushed stone spatters in all directions, he sent out the miserable howling sound, the wound is ripped open by me, the blood spattered in all directions, I settled on the opportunity to hold the butterfly sword directly, calls out attack effect that initiated rides the wind to cut, golden light greatly Sheng, superior god god shape changed the body is more brilliant . Moreover the luck was good, in 15 attacks blew out 10 times of injuries that three times stars exploded continuously, made HP of this lava soldier fall suddenly directly a section!

„Roar!”

Child Queen Shu swinging head, suddenly head one crooked, has bitten the right arm of this lava soldier, stiffly cuts by biting it, that Axe „clang” a landing lava soldier did not have what battle efficiency, child Queen Shu does not give up attacking, the yawn is incorruptible Long Xi, directly the fiery heart of lava soldier cooling, but I take advantage of opportunity a sword, that heart disintegration also means that this lava soldier died in battle officially.

But at this moment behind a bang, was the dark blue billows has used the skill, the long halberd erupted a terrifying to injure, rumbled Frost bangs into the mountain massif, luckily her [Frost Armor] Armor also.

„Frost!” My hurried [say / way].

She actually looks to me, sound is very severe: „Xiao Yao, do not help me , helping child Shu!”

„Good!”

I understand that her meaning, solves the child Shu's match first, then I and child Shu help her together, should three dozens of words, have a stratagem which ensures success? After all Frost now and dark blue billows hit slightly drop the wind, is not the complete inferiority.

Calls out, lava soldier has assumed an awe-inspiring pose, Axe layer on layer chops to divide above my back, really good pain!

„347721!”

This Sif and are high to my attack injury, these lava soldiers are really the goods of strength big non- brain, but I have thousand HP upper limit now, restores 20% every second, is thousand, does not dread this degree of attack, turns round is combo, [Strength of a Thousand Men] rapidly fiercely hits on his body, unexpectedly shook it has drawn back, was really good, in the strength value I did not drop the wind, this was the might of 225% entire attribute additions!

„Does attractively, is this!”

Child Shu sends out Long Yu, the sharp claws numerous rackets after the lava soldier carries on the back, creates fatally strikes the effect, this lava soldier HP were not many, almost soon had been broken to pieces by around the middle the racket, miserable howling, Axe falls on the child Shu's right wing, the blood spatters in all directions, the wound the deep obvious bone, I looked think the pain, but child Shu is Long Shen, the Dragon Clan inborn vitality is formidable, this wound as if could not prevent her from continue fight.

#1340: Landscape beautiful like picture

„You came finally, is really the long in coming!” Dong Cheng Feng stands up, sees the daughter to say with a smile: „Month, sits to father here, a bit faster.”

Dong Cheng Yue definitely wants with me to sit together, but Dong Cheng Feng such does definitely has the reason.

Lin Tiannan clashes my with a smile nod: „Xiao Yao, you come.”

I also nod: „Uncle Lin.”

Saying, I earnestly looked at an old man, afterward bows to salute, said: „Master.”

The old men are very self-satisfied: „Good!”

To come Yang Yanji a powerhouse to be so respectful to him, the old fogy definitely very much enjoys!

„In heard you to play has made the significant progress?” Lin Tiannan asked.

I had not said that nearby Qin Wen said: „Uncle, Li Xiao Yao has completed initially to your commitment, seven big main cities, does not remain takes completely, after over the two days, propaganda that on various game impurities definitely blots out the sky.”

„Really is this, has not thought really that Ha Ha” a Lin Tiannan face happily visits me.

Saying, Lin Tiannan somewhat awkward appearance, was saying with a smile suddenly: „Actually, makes your several come to eat meal today together, the matter must discuss with you.”

I suddenly have to plant not the good premonition: „What matter?”

Dong Cheng Feng teased in side: „Your master called, you can guess that had any important matter.”

„This” I beat a drum.

„Both sides guardians came, this matter” Tang Qi smiled suddenly: „Whoops, I probably was understand anything”

Lin Tiannan stands up, in the hand is carrying one glass of red wines, said: „Actually is not considered as that what important matter, was you and Wan Er, if decided in together, then had free time while me recently, your master also had free time, we held an engagement ceremony first, what kind, your opinions? Does not use embarrassed, here said.”

I and Lin Wan Er flash was shocked.

The matter came suddenly, although we each other deeply loved the opposite party, but married this matter not to think, but the engagement , was a little as if far!

Dong Cheng Yue also side father, silently looks at the tabletop, has not spoken.

Tang Qi had a look at Dong Cheng Yue, in the vision to pass over gently and swiftly not to endure, is gripping tightly the fist.

Yes, Dong Cheng Yue has been in love I, what can I give her? Can't consume others? Perhaps the engagement is also a way of solution.

Stands up slowly, I said: „I want actually, does not know Wan Er”

The Lin Wan Er vision is scalding hot, min the red lip, was saying: „I, if said is not glad, the fellow of your this violence definitely will punch me, I agree!”

Lin Tiannan cannot bear says with a smile joyfully: „Good, I entrusted the subordinate to subscribe the hotel anything's preparation one, about one week, the invitation can send, as for your friends, oneself sent out the invitation to be good.”

„Um.”

At this moment, suddenly Dong Cheng Yue said sentence: „I did not agree.”

„29-day lunar month!”

The Dong Cheng Feng sound was slightly severer, said: „What do you have not to agree?”

It seems like Dong Cheng Feng should also be knows that among us something, he is understood mostly the daughter likes me , will therefore have at this time such performance.

Dong Cheng Yue raises the proud cheek, said: „I did not agree!”

„Why didn't you agree?”

„Because I also want to attend engagement ceremony her voice to be very young with them together”, said: „, Needs the bridesmaid? I must work as”

Lin Tiannan smiles: „Originally is such line, you are the Wan Er best friend, came the bridesmaid to be most appropriate by you, Wan Er didn't you have the opinion?”

Lin Wan Er actually looks at Dong Cheng Yue, the eye was a little red, said the sentence: „Sorry, East city”

Dong Cheng Yue lowered the head, the tears almost fell: „Anything has not sorry, is shallow to reason, can only like this”

The scene is a little awkward, Qin Wen said hurriedly: „We let us not gawk, are eating the thing, can drink a liquor? The service people, come two bottles of red wines, right, wants you most expensive that!”

The old men also stared my one eyes, seemed saying that is your this brat stirs up a good luck!

I am silent, although does not know one have made the mistake anything, but always cannot withdraw the responsibility, but looks at the Dong Cheng Yue appearance, truly thought that loves dearly her, therefore also looked at her two eyes.

Finally was seen by Lin Tiannan, his sigh, shakes the head saying: „Who not young, has not related, Cooldown can destroy all faith, the so-called love, so-called rigid, under the corrosion of Cooldown anything is not, when you arrived at my this age, was anything can see through approximately.”

Tang Qi said: „Uncle Lin penetrating view!”

Lin Tiannan shows a faint smile, starts with Wan Er and I discussed that Cooldown and detail of engagement, the hotel decides in the Hangzhou city best hotel, Cooldown three days later, actually my age can become engaged actually, is Wan Er is a little small, is only 20 years old, the engagement is a little early, but also is only the engagement, has not related.

Is eating, suddenly the cell phone has made a sound, came from Ouyang the telephone of face, after the connection, she very sweet voice passed on, said with a smile: „Xiao Yao, you rested fully, I had worried you were still sleeping, therefore does not dare to disturb.”

„Rests the foot, what matter does face have? Do not weaken my equipment? Let me tell you, I wanted liao to kick, my equipment cannot weaken, otherwise I went to the Consumer Association to sue you to go!”

Ouyang Nuoyan throws smiles: „No, did you regard as that type to telephone not to have the bad woman of good deed me certainly? Relax, this time does not weaken equipment, but wants to ask you to coordinate some technological innovations of our development department, the concrete matter we approximately Cooldown will meet to speak in detail tomorrow, how is it?”

„Is OK, what matter concrete to disclose?”

„Business secret, did not disclose temporarily!”

„Good, then on noon tomorrow together lunch?”

„Um, I invited.”

„Good!”

Continues to discuss that detail of engagement, Lin Tiannan this friend are quite many, it is estimated that over a hundred tables, as for me and Lin Wan Er friend basically are in the games, Li Mu, Wang Jian, Dancing Forest, Q-Sword and Ye Lai these people will definitely come, gathers together, dozens tables, think quite to be extravagant, but has not related, the solemn Tian Xin Corporation little princess becomes engaged, is not grand does not make sense.

This food has eaten around 9 : 00, finally ate to the full.

Returns to the dwelling time around 10 : 00, have gotten online, what should get up to come to see to unify the later map is.

„Brushes!”

A appearance of equipment in Tian Ling Empire, actually saw only the city as if once more to reinforce, the city wall surrounding has cast thick galvanized iron, in addition also cast on many Jing bristles awls, such came the city more difficult to climb, many players are setting up a stall in the city gate, but on my shoulder was reappearing the MVP symbol, opened the package, doing changed the sword, the pure honored sword exchanged.

Immediately a vigorous strength floods into within the body, NND, two world country, had the feeling that the unmatched in the world, who and fights.

Turns on the big map again time, suddenly feels thousand Lijiangshan red, the city on big map, the dense and numerous majorities have marked the place Five-Starred Red Flag has seized, only then dozens secondary host cities in the hand of small server, do not hurt the essentials, they make the inadequate any substantive threat to the Chinese area radically.

Turns over to the sheath the double sword, walking slowly on the main road of city, I now am 255 levels, is full Ji, not wanted not to strive, only if the next edition clears 275 levels, otherwise I now am existence of most peak, in fact truly has reached the peak of this game.

„Drop”, a news came from [Prague] Guildmaster Yanzhao uncle: „Li Xiao Yao, congratulates your!”

„Uncle, what has to be good to congratulate?”

„Haven't you known? After this country fights, your CBN fought the net rank to surpass Fang Ge Que becomes the true first person of Chinese war zone, this was the inside information, I also think that the virtual department has informed you, after 12 : 00 am renovated, you will notice that your CBN fought the net rank is first.”

„Faint, is quick, I also think that also has very big disparity.”

„Ha Ha.” Yanzhao uncle straightforward laughing: „Do not crack a joke, you now are the destiny first person in the true sense, conquers seven big main cities, this is your great achievements, the human spirit that Fang Ge Que accumulated in the past is high, he has not stood in the altitude of your today after all, therefore was surmounted is also normal.”

„Um, that truly must congratulate.” I think, said: „Uncle, I will become engaged the day after tomorrow, flies Hangzhou one?”

„I scratch, do you become engaged? With whom Li Mu or Wang Jian?”

„Go away! Naturally with Wan Er”

„Aha, the Cang Tong goddess became engaged, does not know that many bean noodles must have tears streaming down the face! Helps me arrange the hotel, I am certainly punctual!”

„Good.”

Switches off communication, in guild announced the news that I and Wan Er become engaged, has started a stir immediately, everybody indicated to come, even many people said did not have their invitations also to come Hangzhou to witness the engagement of Guildmaster and vice- Guildmaster, was actually Wan Er was too small, otherwise made us marry according to the Lin Tiannan hot-tempered appointment directly.

Unknowingly has arrived at imperial palace, four imperial guards guarded left a straight military salute: „Holds the spear greatly!”

„Your majesty in?” I asked.

„Your majesty not.” One of them said: „Yesterday your majesty went to the iron skull city to inspect, has not come back, General Situ Xin and General Lin Qiong accompany your majesty to go together, holds the spear not to need to be worried greatly.”

„Um, knew.”

In any case convenient, I from the transmission biography iron removal skull city, later again inquired directly, knew that the shallow forest led 2000 palace guards to go out of town, south iron skull on the seven mountains marking a border of side.

Opened the god shape is changing the body flew, seven mountains marking a border as if were by far exceedingly high general, saw the dense and numerous armies in the direction of summit, the shallow forest.

Speedily flew, jumped to leap close to before, took a step to arrive in front of the king, bowed to salute saying: „Your majesty!”

„Li Master!”

The shallow forest is somewhat excited, says with a smile: „Many thanks Li Master fights a bloody battle for empire wins this powers, you look, this at present the landscape simply is beautiful like the picture.”

I smile, said: „Is your majesty landscape beautiful like the picture.”

The shallow forest stares.

I held the fist in the other hand saying: „Your majesty, I turns in resignation holds the duty of spear greatly, my duty has been accomplished.”

„What?”

Shallow forest shock.

#1348: Rests, friends of mine.

„Has killed him!”

Lin Tiannan the Wan Er protection after behind, low shouting to clear the way of clenching jaws.

One group of bodyguards overran, who once thinks that Wang Ze Cheng took advantage of opportunity to entrain a sturdy steel bar from the floor crack, Yang Yan the enthusiasm emerged, the steel bar instantaneously instantaneous, swept away loudly.

„Bang”

Four the bodyguards of Royal Air levels this were struck to select, Qi Qimen snort is falling to draw back, already severe wound, a self-satisfacation of Wang Ze Cheng face: „What kind, but also who dares to come?”

In this time, „clang”, the long sword that section of roaring flame wrapped was piercing the floor suddenly, I controlled Yang Yan the enthusiasm to run out of the ground, broke the flagstone to arrive in the ground, just horizontally between Wang Ze Cheng and people.

„Brother Xiao Yao”

Yue Qing Qian behind was summoning me in me, she noticed that my clothing many were scratched, even the sound shivered.

Wang Ze Cheng actually laughs, the migration, goes round me suddenly, the hand grasps just likes the fiery red steel bar of leather whip, the foot pedal wall overran, calls out one: „Lin Tiannan Uncle Lin, ten thousand victories want your dog's life to come today!”

Lin Tiannan clenches jaws, protects daughter to retrocede hurriedly.

„Makes way!”

The voice of old man conveys, he kept off in the Wang Ze Cheng front, the double palm transported the perfectly round bracing cold, „” one caught the fiery red steel bar, drank a Royal Air peak the strength to start lowly, the numerous foot trampled to the Wang Ze Cheng abdomen, here captured this weapon for criminal, by the wrestle skill, obviously the old man be higher than several Level to come compared with Wang Ze Cheng, but by the strength, Wang Ze Cheng actually be stronger than the old man.

„Bang”, old man pulled the scalding hot steel bar to draw back continually dozens steps, the face whiten, the steel bar is seizes, but severe wound, the sleeve has almost also burnt.

„Mother!”

Old K roars, the natural disposition of street ruffian reveals completely with nothing left, worked on a chair entraining the ferroguinous chair leg, the direct impact on Wang Ze Cheng, the violent shouted to clear the way: „Protects Wan Er and Uncle Lin, our that many people, but also fears a Wang Ze Cheng such bastard?”

Wolf has also smashed a chair, although does not have any too big skill, the guts that but my group of brothers go all out even must be bigger than these bodyguards!

How can make them brave hardships and dangers?

I had speedily caught up at this time, the long sword was unconstrained flame air wave bang to approach the back of Wang Ze Cheng.

„!”

The Wang Ze Cheng cry likely is not a human, the back has given birth to green rock shape scales unexpectedly, „bang” surges butterfly sword Mars to fly upwards, but strength of Yang Yan the has separated enters his body spatially, my body flies high, the sword potential one old immediately has raised the left fist, gathers the full flame strength on the vertebra of bang after his brain on!

„Bang!”

Numerous fist, poured into the three visceral cavities and gall bladder flame vigor not to go, even the flame was passing the skin and scales in the body of combustion Wang Ze Cheng, changed into the average person already my these two to be struck unravelling, although the Wang Ze Cheng physique was strong, but also already not being able to withstand gradually, but he clenched teeth to support, the body flushed forward, suddenly a long-handled fan!

In the clear sound, Old K and chair leg in Wolf broke, simultaneously Wang Ze Cheng false „Yang Yanjin” puts out, immediately Old K and a Wolf launching draws back, two arms both seriously distorted, was about the bone fracture.

Surroundings, one group of people pull out weapon aiming Wang Ze Cheng, the next quarter stormy sound of gunfire resounds, large flames spit to this S level breed to think of the human, Wang Ze Cheng raise head to laugh, his even eyes, mouth and ear leave have the careful scale protection, basic on the fires of fearless these bullets.

I raise the sword horizontally between Wang Ze Cheng and Wan Er, the vision was dim, said: „Are you how is it?”

Wang Ze Cheng has smiled, smiles extremely miserably: „I soon had all, but as a result of your existence, I lost all, you said that what I do want to make?”

I the butterfly in front, the treasured sword that this handle destroyed the hardest defenses presented volume mouths and cracks slowly horizontally, is similar to my present body is ordinary, gained ground to have a look at him, I said: „You have defeated, this is the fact, I give you an opportunity, independent combat with me, we minute of victory and defeat, decides the life and death, how is it? If you have liked Wan Er, that kills me, this is you best proof.”

„Does not want!” Lin Wan Er said hurriedly loudly: „Our that many people, why can you also brave hardships and dangers obviously?”

I crack into a smile: „Wan Er, do not speak, this is the I and Wang Ze Cheng matter, we must have a showdown eventually, that elects today!”

Lin Tiannan is holding daughter's shoulder, said in a low voice: „Wan Er, obeys the Li Xiao Yao words, right that he said.”

Actually, we understand, if Wang Ze Cheng must massacre our several people at risk of life, I could not block, but we lose were too many, Ah Lei and Shen Bing death, has sufficed, cannot some people lose the life again for this reason.

Wang Ze Cheng smiles grieved, in the palm is dense the roaring flame, said: „Good, if I defeat you, I will pinch to explode your head, will also carry off Wan Er, here all people, snort do not want to go on living.”

He said very superficially, as if the life and death insignificantly was in his eyes same.

Mu Xuan is nipping the silver tooth: „Was insane, was simply insane”

Fang Ge Que sits in the wheelchair, said lightly: „Mu Xuan, do not speak, do not speak, has a look Old K and Wolf Totem, their injuries probably need to wrap up, you have studied the first aid, has a look.”

„Um!”

The ZGTV staff who Fei Er brings to photograph this engagement ritual, as a program that on the game channel broadcasts, is the present completely is different, the staff hands and feet of ZGTV shivers, courage Ju Lie in live transmission this god demon showdown, the body of Wang Ze Cheng the person non- person and ghost were not clever, but my whole body is lingering dozens flame remnant Armor, similarly likely is not the ordinary people, our showdowns, being no different is the decisive battle between god and demon.

„After all people, falls back on the corner!”

I open the arm, strength of unceasing spitting Yang Yan enter in the butterfly sword, simultaneously small sound track in communication: „Axe, erects your electromaguetic rail gun, locks on the S goal, if I have defeated, gets rid decisively, do not make him injure and innocent.”

Axe nod: „OK, the boss refuels!”

The vision sweeps, Xing Lie also appeared in the distant place, a sniper's rifle of every shot hits the target by him in the staircase, here the straight direction, I also felt relieved horizontally like this.

„Come!” I show a faint smile to Wang Ze Cheng.

This smiling face seems an insult, Wang Ze Cheng has the feeling that a sleepy beast fights, roared to clash lowly, in close that moment that a hand and foot and used I also the sword, the flame butterfly sword in airborne slightly has shaken, the spiral flame bracing cold swallowed on his shoulder, what made me not think was Wang Ze Cheng is going all out unexpectedly, when butterfly „tittering” drilled into his within the body, his sharp claws also revolved, but, „bang” a sound bang in my abdomen!

Flame remnant Armor disintegration several pieces, HP was turbulent, the formidable strength is makes me fly high to fall to draw back, returns to the rest suddenly, supports the ground single-handed, after flying high to turn several, fell to the ground.

Just fell to the ground Wang Ze Cheng to come, the whole body was wrapping the roaring flame, the flame sharp claws slanting swept away.

How could to make him act in a self-serving manner like this?

My moral nature anger, both hands grip tightly a butterfly sword sword to swing suddenly, an under foot wrong step, the dodging character Secret Art in riding the wind swordsmanship, appears behind his side suddenly, the butterfly sword rocks, erupts 78 swords to fall on his scales instantaneously, chops scale dispersing to spatter in all directions, the blood crossflow, he likely is the wild animal general is roaring, calls out one one pitch-dark, brings the tail of pointed cone to break the pants to extend from the back, that is long from the vertebra, he truly already complete mutation.

„!”

Tail iron whip same brushing on my arm, burning ache, but I have not retroceded, an instantaneous body sinking right leg of landing sweeps away, sweeps the Wang Ze Cheng huge body turned at the same time exploding from bottom to top to kick a foot! „Bang” Wang Ze Cheng has almost not been able to fall to the ground, but my spin body body situated in him, both hands has pushed the ground fiercely, then the formidable counter- tension to airborne continuously is trampling four feet, the flame spurts to open, Wang Ze Cheng , the scale that carries on the back piece by piece has also fallen off.

Nobody cheered, all people have turned very quiet.

Not far away, Q-Sword grips tightly thin sword, the whole body air current is lingering, his formal clothes slowly stirs, the Tang Qi hand is grasping the throwing knife, the vision is staring at us, is protecting proximally, once I fell into the dangerous situation, he can first Cooldown get rid without a doubt, this was a friend, a farther place, the Drunken Spear form also appeared, the legend he was a follower, now looks like truly is this, he defended in Yan Zhao Warrior, Fang Ge Que and Mu Xuan front, weaponless, but around the fist was lingering the wind rest.

„Wan Er is my!”

In the Wang Ze Cheng mouth is flowing the blood, actually fierce bending down visits me on the ground.

On the butterfly sword in my hand presented several giant volume mouths and openings, actually in the heart fights intent to be soaring, is angry: „Has sufficed, for your selfish desire, how many people you harmed dead a tragic death, did you still remember Dong Cheng Lei? Do you still remember Shen Bing?”

„Dong Cheng Lei, an idiot, died died, what Zuxi? Shen Bing, that policewoman? Ha, before she dies I have not let under enjoy her body, was really a pity!” Wang Ze Cheng is laughing.

My short of breath launches a psychological attack, leapt the step to clash, Yang Yan the bracing cold has arrived at boundary more than enough, imposing manner locking, the flame pressure has kept Wang Ze Cheng from fending, the butterfly sword layer on layer pricked in his chest cavity.

„Ah Lei is not an idiot, he is the world best elder brother!”

My short distance looks at a he fierce face, shouted to clear the way lowly: „Shen Bing damn, she should freely live around us, your this bastard, was you have killed them!”

When Wang Ze Cheng quack laughs, goes crazy the swaying from side to side body, „Bang” wrenched apart the butterfly stiffly, the fist also fell on my chest, several flame remnant Armor were destroyed.

I do not go to control these aches, jumps is a knee hit on his chin, is in airborne both hands to grip the sword hilt, the flame strength emerges crazily, before Wang Ze Cheng falls to the ground on numerous breaks the sword to prick in his chest the butterfly!

„Hong!”

The roaring flame puts out completely, burnt down his heart rapidly, broke the sword to puncture thoroughly his body directly, sewed him on the floor.

„”

Wang Ze Cheng crazy is struggling, but has not helped matters, the heart and bloodlines were fired the flying ash that moment, his body no longer moves finally, in the eye pupil also lost the appearance, this Buesst youngest CEO died finally.

Whole body shivers to be incapable, I knelt by the Wang Ze Cheng corpse slowly, in the mind recalled all sorts of passing, could not bear nose acid, began supinely does not make the tears fall, said loudly: „Ah Lei, the Xiao Yao elder brother revenged for you! Shen Bing, Li Youngster revenged for you! Your soul in heaven, rest!”

#1368: Mystical new map

The moonlit night plain, length and breadth land situated in iron skull city West, here is one piece herded the region, is living wild horse, antelope, prairie wolf and other animals, but these animals have not existed now, what replaces it is a dense and numerous crowd, at least tens of millions people crowded gather on the plain, is in the majority by the common people.

However their weapons likely are not so are wise, many people who Wan Er said even take are cutting the bread the shovel of knife and hoeing and other clumsy iron hardware, absolutely does not have what battle efficiency.

„Really is the peasant uprising” short spear trick sighed that said one.

I also somewhat sighed that ordered: „Heavy shield camp, the lineup, they do not attack, we cannot attack on own initiative!”

„Yes!” The Han deep pool nods.

One crowd raised emphatically the barbarian palace guard in abundance cloth of shield has become shield, the vault of heaven armed forces, the strong wind from afar armed forces and fall harvest armed forces in abundance lineup, was also orderly with our arrays, equipment complete compared with, the army of opposite party simply really looked like one group of motley crew.

„Thump”

The long blade in Han deep pool revolved slightly, he stares at the front, in the eye is passing an awkwardness, turns around to look to me: „Your highness, can we really with these almost weaponless common people fight?”

„They were misled, has become the enemy in empire, if they act willfully, can regard as the brave fighter them.” My light saying, some are not at heart happy, actually I am same as Han Yuan, we are willing to challenge the powerful match, but does not rely on with these common people who bullies the weak battles.

Still remembers that initially our pledge was „fights for the weak one”, what now our are the actions?

Suddenly, my heart like is receives the heavy blows to strike, is quite uncomfortable, but otherwise, can we be what kind of? Looks that the righteousness pledge crushes Tian Ling Empire, looks that our many brothers like this have all efforts wasted with the road of King the blood does pave? No, we cannot achieve, at this moment, only has to take up the butcher knife, this is our only choices.

„Thump”

The distant place, battle drum sound starts to thunder, behind the numerous peasant armed forces has the army, their battle drum sounds were starting to urge that the farmer armed forces started attack.

The front line, on throws over worn-out Pi Jia, in the hand is grasping a farmer armed forces leader of handle short sword to raise the short sword high, on the face is angry and shouts oneself hoarse is bellowing: „Compatriots, to be free, for equality, attack! We are since birth equal, is always not the slave of this group of empire running dogs, the attack!”

Was unavoidable!

My vision one cold, said: „Archer prepares, shoots their offensive!”

One group of heavy cavalries have raised the bow crossbow in abundance, the tidal farmer armed forces flushed, was distanced to shoot less than 100 meters time our bow and arrow, spread the day to block out the sun, flash blood incarnadine earth, crowded arrow arrow „puff puff” in the body of injection innocent people, casualty many people, but these people were very crazy, after many people arrow, actually as before forward dashed about wildly.

„Is this believes the equal the strength?” Jing Yin dumbfounded standing there, making her dance the long sword to meet these weaponless people, she cannot achieve.

Even linked many archers to slow down the speed of archery, they same were not cruel enough.

„Bang bang bang”

The flesh and blood hit on the heavy shield of palace guard, these is the person of doughhead and farmer raised „pointed weapons” in abundance, pricks in the bread blade and manure fork the mail-armor and helmet of palace guard, a blood spatters in all directions, we are not willing to kill them, but they actually in crazy is slaughtering our soldiers.

Clenches teeth suddenly, I hold up long sword, said loudly: „Attack!”

The front palace guard already felt suffocated, raises the long blade in abundance, cuts off the head of opposite party, quick what person had scruples the match on nobody again is, in their eyes, these farmers and doughheads were the enemies, can kill own enemy.

The player team also launched the offensive, Li Mu and Wang Jian has led the [Zhan Long] melt god cavalry to advance the past, was almost slaughtering by the potential of conquering by killing.

The both sides great disparity in strength, less than farmer armed forces of a half hour of opposite party the rout in population insufficient 10% China area crack troops, this large-scale duty was hurried, the player who coming is also insufficient thousand, in addition NPC army also on thousand, in population absolute inferiority, but in the strength is actually the superiority of crush.

Fresh common people degenerated into corpse, when their battle losses surpass 10%, many people started the rout to flee and become separated, this is also the result that I want, the peasant uprising, was killed to exceed 10% times should also total military defeat.

Dead ahead, distant has heard hoofbeat, is the army of North Sea city, probably the thousand person high and low appearance , a cutting edge military officer is raising the lance, one time punctures military deserter common people suddenly selects to kill, on the face full is the spunk, loudly exclaimed: „Righteousness pledge big deacon and North Sea city god Sir Hou leads to come personally, the people do not fear the despotic power of empire running dog, we can achieve this success!”

Hears the name of righteousness pledge big deacon, many military deserters looked like have knocked medicine same rapid turning head, turned around to attack to kill.

Was this wave has attacked, the army that so long as we defeated the North Sea city god marquis won total victories!

„Attacks their main camps!”

I am ordering loudly, opens the god shape to lead Wan Er, Yue Qing Qian and the others to advance forward, the army of main heavy cavalry and North Sea city of palace guard attacks in together, but Li Mu and Wang Jian immediately understanding leads the [Zhan Long] melt god cavalry to cover from the flank kills the impact, the left is Q-Sword leads one crowd of [Hero’s Mound] riding war to be the player attacks, has been doomed in the flash of contact the defeat of North Sea city army.

It is not out of the anticipation, less than the thousand armies in 20 minutes of North Sea city on the rout, they were only a NPC army of secondary host city, how also possibly was first under heaven city Tian Ling Empire the match of NPC army.

Distant, saw the colors of North Sea city god marquis, but I killed the past time does not see the person's shadow, sees only distant place mist and dust, Han Yuanti the long blade was saying: „That nonsense god marquis ran away, Sir, what to do can we, pursue?”

„Pursues!”

I said without hesitation: „Massacres this any North Sea god marquis, even if were stills this rebels.”

„Yes!”

On plain in great confusion, many Tian Ling Empire players are chasing down the common people of revolting to gain to put down a rebellion recklessly points, although somewhat despises, but I am unable to prevent, is being killed by them, although this game designs more and more user-friendly and exquisite, but many people regard a game it after all as before, what human nature since is the game also discusses and morals?

The Tian Ling Empire army pursues the several thousand defeated troops of North Sea god marquis to head west, they have not stayed, we have not stayed, in addition also has [Zhan Long], [Hero’s Mound] and [Prague] three big Guild players, was also towed as for [Legend], [Judgement] and other Guild in behind, because has encountered one group of US war zone players' interception, had a fierce battle mostly.

On the plain the cold wind howls, here map as if has renovated, when with my previous time comes Chi You tribe terrain not to be completely different, most remarkable is in the south border region, the map ZONE direction presented a piece of continuous mountain range, above the mountain range has soared to the heavens the barrier together, looked from afar somewhat was actually magnificent.

„Is Xishan.”

Yan Zhao Warrior pouts, said: „Map that recently brushed, but nobody can pass Xishan, does not know that this North Sea god marquis is making any ghost.”

I knit the brows: „Somewhat was always tempted feeling, nearby this Xishan definitely has the ambusher.”

Q-Sword smiled: „Xiao Yao you were too oversuspicious, knot of Xishan is map ZONE, did not have the map toward the west again, the player and NPC could not pass!”

„Right?” The Lin Wan Er delicate eyebrows raise, are pointing at the distant place: „Do you have a look at the army of North Sea city to do?”

„Um?”

Q-Sword looked at the past, actually discovery that was called „North Sea god marquis” launched a golden reel, the reel has sent out to soar to the heavens the ray, opened a front door on map ZONE knot rapidly, his army filed.

„Does the ZONE south have map?” Q-Sword in great surprise.

„We what to do?” Yan Zhao Warrior asked.

„So long as solves North Sea god marquis, we can solve the righteousness pledge to be chaotic, after all he is the righteousness pledge big deacon, but also with consideration?” I show a faint smile: „Is great we dead in this mystical map, does not have anything at the worst.”

Yan Zhao Warrior laughs: „Good, I am also this want to result, attack!”

Xiao Yao Wang Heda held the spear to achieve consistently, immediately in the ground the mist and dust was billowing, palace guard, vault of heaven armed forces, fall harvest armed forces and other Tian Ling Empire the armies have crashed in map ZONE the crack in abundance, who knows that was waiting for in another side what we were, perhaps was an opportunity and challenge? Plays the game, for is a risk, if this does not dare to challenge, that also plays the game to make anything.

When I control raspberry overruns, only thought that at present one bright, the surroundings turned into another picture, unexpectedly the extraordinary beautiful scenery, on the big map a twinkle, the map name turned into „north boundary forest” from Xishan, moreover is an ultra-large map.

„!”

A Yan Zhao Warrior face is astonished: „Has the map really!”

Q-Sword laughs: „Is very good, the big map of destiny renovated really completely has extended, looked like we are the first batch since the person of new map, the luck was good!”

I nod, look to the distant place, the thousand + defeated troops of North Sea god marquis am dashing about wildly toward the distant place as before, but a sky gloom, looks like as if must rain.

„Pursues, rained destroyed completely god Hou Jun before!”

„Yes!”

The oppression of the people able to move unhindered above the earth, were getting more and more since the player and NPC of new map, has formed a grand theater curtain bedding above the earth, however, in the massive players and NPC after the new map, the sky stuffy thunder fell suddenly together, the earth shivered fiercely, the backdrop of distant place was snapping unexpectedly!

„How?” Yan Zhao Warrior turns around to shout to clear the way loudly.

Lin Qiong holds the fist in the other hand saying: „Holds the spear greatly, one mystical strength is closing the space potential surface, we as if were closed here!”

„This” Yan Zhao Warrior could not speak.

I looked at a package, as expected, City Return Scroll is pessimistic, here is unable to return to the city.

#1369: Our graves?

„What's the matter?” Lin Wan Er rides in the silver dragon carries on the back, raises head to look at the sky, saw only in the world as if instantaneous tarnish many to be the same.

I shake the head: „Does not know how, to feel we entered others' trap.”

„The map of new edition?” Li Mu said.

„Perhaps, hoping is this.” I have a look at the front enormous and powerful palace guard, unavoidably some worries.

Yue Qing Qian raises the dagger, under god shape is treading is saying with a smile void: „Brother Xiao Yao, we do not manage that many, kills directly, what god marquis the person of that massacres, the duty has also been accomplished, perhaps here knot can lift a ban?”

„Um , can only like this.”

A butterfly sword finger, issues an order the later three services to overrun forward together, but the top right-hand corner of game contact surface presented population System Notification, in the human total since new map is thousand, moreover is just thousand.

Saw this digit time I am the moral nature sink, some restless feelings, we entered others' trap.

However North Sea god marquis also on that person, at all possibly is not our matches, has their ambushers in the front jungle? Should be insufficient is right!

Speeds away for nearly one hour to south, the new map compared with the wanting length and breadth that we imagined, the horizon reduced slowly, quick, a giant city appeared in our fields of vision, that was the city that a green city wall brick laid on top of one another becomes, the scale was probably similar to the highest heaven city, is the moderate scale in first-level host city, on the map also gradually appeared the name ghost town of this city.

„Ghost town?” Yan Zhao Warrior knitting the brows head, „this name, this anything ghost thing!”

I have not spoken, at this moment, ting flutters in the ear

„Bites!”

System System Notification: You have stepped into the foreign country city 【Ghost town】 In domain!

Map introduction: The ghost town, city of the perishing, the legend before the Flood ghost town was one of the world seven big famous cities, stands erect in the tumultuous times that successive years went on an expedition not but actually, one generation of Ming glistened the Great Emperor to assume the city of this productivity, why however no one knew, overnight the ghost town degenerated into city of the nobody, nobody knows that which these humanity went, took Xishan as, the entire empire shut off with the northern domain, isolates into two potential surfaces, perished in light of this, however in the later generation exploration, the ghost town unveiled her mystical veil eventually, please must be careful, enters the ghost town. Later, you will face the danger and challenge that some are unable to imagine, if conquers the ghost town successfully, the area will save from the darkness entire south, opens the new time!

„Is this enlightenment duty of new map?” Q-Sword asked.

Xue Rou nods: „Properly speaking is this, but was also difficult saying that always felt we were been cloudy.”

Jian Feng Han said: „Manages his many, first butchered that North Sea god Hou Zai saying that he was the righteousness pledge big deacon, was the chief criminal of entire item matter, killed him to complete the task.”

„Um!”

At this moment, the ghost town city gate opens loudly, several thousand people of North Sea god marquis enter the city in abundance, when we rush the city has closed.

Luckily, the Long Jing artillery and invincible might artillery of palace guard and vault of heaven armed forces still, like this us had facing the qualification of any crisis.

Rapid [Enemies at the Gate], the Tian Ling Empire four big regiment sur- players, the total about 1 million, city of the nobody is unable to resist us obviously, is raising the butterfly sword, I bring Wan Er, East city, Li Mu, Wang Jian and Xue Rou and the others to stand outside the city gate in not far away the sky, ordered the later Long Jing artillery to start to bomb.

On the city, the NPC army of North Sea city deploys troops for defense in the city wall, the archer pulls open the bowstring to aim at us in distant place, what a pity can too be really small to the damage that we cause.

Has a look at behind people, I said: „Sends out few people, first enters the ghost town to investigate from space, believes firmly that in the city did not have what ambush to say again.”

„Oh.”

Everybody diverges rapidly, I raised the long sword rapidly to fly from the city gate, opened the shield of standard hand summon stars to keep off the innumerable arrow arrows, was pasting the city main road to the forward flight in the past, actually only saw that shops were the front door shut tightly, the stove of blacksmith's shop several thousand years had probably not ignited, in the bakery was also an emptiness, the only living creature was these bustles about in the city is constructing the North Sea city army of fortification, and they should also be the first arrival, was not ripe winds the terrain.

„Crash-bang!”

A spin body has crashed in residents in city, pushed the front door loudly to collapse gently, took a step in the noses was filling decayed smell, toward , the ashes in fireplace has corrupted again traceless, the chair in main hall bumped gently completely has become pile of powder powders, went upstairs to have a look, in several rooms also nobody, the quilt completely decayed has become one pile of fragments.

Underground!

Raises the long sword to enter the basement, an extraordinary putrefactive odor transmits, this basement was used to preserve food, in glass jars the souse once food, as if was also having the appearance of strawberry jam, but definitely not nice-smelling, that many years, already fermented one bunch of stinking things.

Lifts the hand, „clang” pricks the bottom the long sword, has unearthed several rice depth furiously, does not have any discovery as before.

Leaps the body, continued to search for common people residence as well as barracks on several other streets, anything discovered does not have, had proven to the underground from the space this city was a dead city, some people will not lay an ambush to us in the city.

„What does your side have to harvest?” Asked in team channel.

Lin Wan Er: „No, anything does not have.”

Yue Qing Qian: „Um, here is also.”

Old K: „This truly is a dead city, mother, soaks the dog deng not to have!”

Xue Rou: „I go, old K you were also too vulgar, Brother Xiao Yao kicks the team this goods quickly, he drew lowered our overall quality levels, hee hee”

I also laugh: „Do not make, the atmosphere is so serious!”

Lin Wan Er said: „That present what to do, husband?”

„Orders to attack a city comprehensively!” My diving posture in the space, looks at the city four directions the air-to-air fertile plain, said: „This map we know nothing, does not know that can have any unknown thing in waiting to attack us, therefore we should better take this ghost town as the foundation of foothold first, otherwise when faces the thunderbolt possibly has become confused, we exit, assist to attack a city, do not use Long Jing artillery, in the situation of not destroying the city takes four Daijouike, captures alive that North Sea god marquis.”

„OK!”

I have pasted the rapid flight, a troop North Sea city army exudes the roaring sound to raise the shield to come to square to keep off emphatically, but where can block, all had driven out by my one set of skill, simultaneously Lin Wan Er drops from the clouds, the silver dragon howls a dragon rest also to make these NPC armies unable to bear completely, skill that in addition the silver spear strikes, destroys completely a troop person rapidly.

„Wife you defend, I kick the gate!” I raise the double sword to laugh.

The Lin Wan Er defensive power is less inferior than me many, the whole body surpasses 30% [Drain] effects, naturally does not dread with these NPC soldiers engages in hand-to-hand combat, the consecutively several skills have massacred one group of people, likely is a beautiful small devil, said smilingly: „You a bit faster, we left the Tian Ling Empire domain, always makes me feel somewhat restlessly.”

„Um.”

Actually restless far more than is she, thinks including me somewhat restlessly, rapidly goes forward, [Blade Rush] broke through stop of one crowd of NPC, the god shape changes the attack effect that under the body rumbles to ride the wind to cut suddenly, immediately tears into shreds one group of people, before rushing, fights a boots loudly foot, „”, the giant steel and iron door bolt after iron gate such kicked out of the way horizontally!

„”

The outside innumerable palace guards flushed under leadership of Han deep pool, this city gate announced that was solved!

„Your highness!”

Jing Yin progresses to come, said grinningly: „Such with ease broke the city, your highness military might!”

I nod: „Quickly seizes the entire city, the armies of some multi- captive North Sea cities, capture alive the god marquis . Moreover, all advances the city to erect the heavy artillery, prepares for that defends a city.”

„Yes!”

Four big city gates in 20 minutes on the entire tribe in our hands, remaining was one has slaughtered, the tens of thousands remnants in North Sea city naturally were not our matches, insisted the person who revolted against killed completely, kept one to assign as for these people of disarming, I also want to obtain something from their mouths, after all we knew nothing about here.

After near one hour of street fighting, ended the fight rapidly, cuts to add up totals ten thousand people, captures 7000 + people.

Without the armed forces account, therefore in the square of city center, all captives was bound in the same place, but numerous military officer also respectful standing from Tian Ling Empire on square stair, waits for me to give orders, although I am only a Xiao Yao king of director, as if my status militarily in the mind of people must high in a big way holds Yan Zhao Warrior of spear by far.

Yan Zhao Warrior is somewhat helpless, I somewhat am also helpless, it seems like only when I leave this game thoroughly time, uncle's three services marshal position can true straightening up, really be painstakingly he!

„In the past, honest!”

The Han deep pool raised a chicken to raise a person to come likely, was that North Sea god marquis, when we saw this person could not bear smile, god Hou in this legend unexpectedly only then about 1.6 meters appearance, looked like very short, the armor of military might put on laughable that his body could not say.

„Wait / Etc.!”

My diving posture goes down the stair, is holding the both arms of god marquis, scolds to say to the Han deep pool: „Do not be impolite!”

„Yes!” Acting in a play of Han deep pool coordination.

I help up the god marquis, but when his look contacts me, makes one that my innermost feelings cannot bear shock, what look that is, floods angry and contemptuous, is teasing and wins, what he has made to us, will have such look?

„God marquis, you is a captive.” I said.

He raises head with a smile, said: „Come Li Xiao Yao, you are that world civilizing role of government Wugong first person, this I have to acknowledge, however in this world, hey, after you have killed me, naturally can understand all.”

„Your what meaning?” I asked.

The god marquis sneers: „I sacrificed 100,000 soldiers, attracts here the running dogs of your empire emperors, aren't you clear? Li Xiao Yao, only if you can live are going out of this foreign country, otherwise waits for death, do not think that the ghost town can save you, here is one for your preinstall good grave!”

I: „”

#1371: Mystical Giants army

In all person vision projects frightened, I am raising the long sword, spins the body to fly, draws out from the city wall brick that steel arrow, pulls out that bloody number of people slowly, nearby palace guard looks fear, they have experienced the life and death struggle, but has not seen such death shape, benefits the head of arrow penetration person, is this big strength?

„Army prepares, the shield crosses top!” I order to say loudly.

Not merely is the NPC army, the player also has lifted the top the shield, no one dares to question in the dense fog the strength of invading enemy, even if the monster, possibly is also the strength completely the monster above us!

„What ghost?!” The Yan Zhao Warrior complexion is pale.

Lin Qiongti the long sword, was saying: „Your highness, the future is bad they to hide in the dense fog, we occupied completely the inferiority”

At this moment, suddenly in dense fog „whiz whiz whiz” was about hundred giant arrow arrows has shot, the accurate aim was not very accurate, but in the strength strong, deep injection city wall, some shot on the shield of palace guard, unexpectedly penetrated the shield directly, shot through the chest of palace guard soldier, this strength really went against heaven's will!

I looked at the heart to tremble, lifted the hand saying: „Long Jing artillery, aims at dense fog, bombing!”

„Bang bang bang”

In the city wall shivers, Long Jing artillery is spitting large flame firing off, mushroom cloud shock-waves surge in the dense fog under city, the storm that produces rapidly has also blown off the dense fog, at this time we saw the dense fog invading enemy in finally, impressively is height at least 5 meters humanity, but is not the food transvestite and mountain ridge giant that clumsy giant, but wears the armor, pretty humanity, but the build has gone far beyond us.

They are wearing the bow and arrow, kills the arrow arrows of our soldier from there, stands in the dense fog, even if were bombed after by Long Jing artillery and invincible might artillery, actually gorgeously not but actually, but was the sincere armor is torn, the thigh and abdomen bled to continue, the battle efficiency, their armor was too as before sincere, like was the armored vehicle, Long Jing artillery as if how.

„Exercise”

Li Mu clenches teeth saying: „Is this what gadget, the army of which empire? We had not run into such match before!”

I nod, said: „First has a look at this gadget the attribute to be what kind of!”

Yue Qing Qian actually shakes the head saying: „Useless Brother Xiao Yao, my skill can the detection of very-long-range monster Level and attribute, but these time could not see that can only see their Level is 275 levels, the attribute cannot see.”

„275 levels?”

I knit the brows: „Is this omen that 275 levels of editions clear? What matter but our sleepily here this is, whose offline telephones, asks game official what situation?”

Yan Zhao Warrior shakes the head: „Useless, I made the human ask, Ouyang Nuoyan said that our that many player and NPC army since the new map was the system independent hypothesis production, the gizmondo cannot change the procedure, needed us to go through a strategic pass to escape, even if were many players sues is also useless, because the gizmondo was helpless.”

Jian Feng Han narrows the eyes to focus, pair of straight eyebrows slanting upwards and outwards raise, said with a smile: „Xiao Yao, did you also rather too high look at these giants? Is stronger besides the strength, they not necessarily are our matches, does not fight to defeat, this is not your style!”

I nod, but the moral nature somewhat is serious, these giant soldiers as if are the strengths that the North Sea god marquis takes advantage, since North Sea god Hou Gan attracts here us with the life, he certainly thinks that the strength of this mystical giant army can defeat us, therefore the strength of this army is not simple!

„How don't they have the sound?” Wan Er asked in side.

I am also vacant: „Does not know that their archery are very as if bad . Moreover the arrow arrow quantity of carrying are not many, attacks a city to be also not necessarily able to grab any bargain forcefully!”

Saying, was ordering: „Palace guard, saves the shell, when they approached again the saturation bombing!”

„Yes, Your highness!” The Han deep pool nod meets the command.

At this time, [Prague] Guild some warhawks rode to search the player to ascend to heaven, went to the low altitude to investigate the further information of this mystical army, however, when they arrived above the giant soldier top of the head, these giant soldiers worked on behind was shouldering the wire rope unexpectedly rapidly, „whiz whiz whiz” the throwing heaven, rode to search warhawks pulls down forcefully, draws out Axe and great sword, one has hacked to death, the strength value was much higher!

„I held” Yan Zhao Warrior deeply to attract an cold air/Qi, said: „Was too fearful”

He was somewhat flustered.

Q-Sword has licked the lip, said: „Archery, although is very bad, however belays is much higher!”

„How do I feel them in what?” Dong Cheng Yue said.

Lin Wan Er nods together: „Um, I have this feeling.”

I clench teeth: „Sent the assassin to be player [Stealth] in the past, had a look at this giant army many population.”

Yue Qing Qian nods, soon, returns to report: „Brother Xiao Yao, their total numbers of people probably in thousand about, do not arrive at our 1/10, actually we have the stratagem which ensures success.”

„Was difficult saying that they were 275 levels, many of us did not have the full level, Level was disparate, will be killed by the second.”

„They came!” Jian Feng Han somewhat excited looks at the distant place.

Really, among these giant soldier each people are distanced about 10 meters, has formed the array, the rear more giant soldiers came, and is hauling giant freight vehicles, on the vehicle is placing great crags.

„What do they want to make?” Wan Er opened the bright eyes.

„Definitely does not have good deed” my moral nature to tremble.

„They must attack a city with the stone!” Yan Zhao Warrior is gripping tightly the long sword.

The voice has not fallen, the distant place has transmitted startled day whooshing, Giants soldier both arms brandish a great crag, roared throwing the great crag, that several tons stone departed several hundred meters in his hands unexpectedly directly!

„!”

The sole trembles suddenly, the stone pounded a gulf in the city wall directly, in a flash, I and Yan Zhao Warrior looked at one another, the heart quick was cool, what we faced was what enemy?

„Long Jing artillery, aims at them, did not use the frugal shell!” I order loudly.

The words that yes, we do not counterattack perhaps, this frail ghost town quickly must degenerate into the ruins, once the city wall damages, our ground cavalry soldiers facing tyrannical of match, really are also the unmatcheds in the world?

The airborne, one after another great crag broken wind comes.

I jump hurriedly, the opening god shape, raises the shield of protection city wall stars, „” a bang, that great crag like is the shell hits on the shield of stars, I am also the whole body tremble, the tough value of shield of stars fell instantaneously about one-third, was this hitting power rather too also terrorist? Is two bang pounds, the shield of stars dispersed.

„The Xiao Yao elder brother, we came!”

Wang Jian, Li Mu, Matcha and the others open the god shape to block one after another in the city front, brandishes the pointed weapons to cut these great crags, but basic on cutting, the stone was too big, like is the truck the big stone, who can block?

„Bang bang bang” sound is unceasing, dozens god shape players in airborne quick could not resist, HP fell below half, but these giants actually as in continually threw the great crag, around the ghost town in the city wall rapidly has also been being scarred, no wonder North Sea god Hou said that here was our grave, it seems like truly possibly can like this.

I somewhat am fearful, the crack troops of day plume empire here, entire palace guards completely, vault of heaven armed forces, fall harvest armed forces and flame Long Jun and others here, once whole army has been annihilated, this to Tian Ling Empire absolutely is lethality hitting hard, the shallow forest must guard the landscape by these armies, I have actually taken this dead end them.

In a flash, hundred taste weeds, lament at heart angrily with mixed in the same place.

„Bang!”

The great crag falls in the city wall, pounded pile of hashed meat one group of palace guard soldiers, afterward was full is in the bloodstain rolling into city, has been battered to death many players, a Cooldown entire ghost town fell into the thick death fear up and down.

„Mother, cannot be like this passive!”

Jian Feng Han is grasping the long sword, said: „Perhaps Xiao Yao, we such passively got down to be broken the city again to slaughter, died passively, could win on own initiative, I must lead the [Vanguard] brothers to go out of town seek battle on own initiative, you?”

„Going out of town field operation?”

My moral nature sinks: „It is not good, temporarily does not know their ground battle strength is what kind, perhaps goes out of town is bringing death, we defend a city have the heavy artillery to support for the time being, went out of town does not have on any superiority!”

The Jian Feng Han brow raises: „But defends in the city dies, that was also too aggrieved, you lead troops to be discrete I to know, or this, I lead the [Vanguard] thousand player to go out of town, tries water, how is it?”

I look to Yan Zhao Warrior: „Uncle, do you think? Q-Sword, your opinion?”

Yan Zhao Warrior opens the god shape to avoid a great crag bang to pound, bending down in an extremely difficult situation on the ground, said: „This is also means that the player who however goes out of town was not necessarily able to come back, this was real.”

Q-Sword said: „thousand person are too few, Jian Feng Han, I have the [Hero’s Mound] main force to go with you together, we crowd together, in addition some NPC armies, can have the 200 000 player military strength, can fight!”

„Um!” In the Jian Feng Han eye brings to be excited and grateful.

Hence, two war duplicate class grandmaster players must fight finally shoulder to shoulder.

I also said: „Your Guild in together how many people?”

„thousand person.” Q-Sword said.

„Good, I give thousand again flame Sergeant Long the soldier to you, adds up to 200 000, if the fight is smooth, I have other main forces to go out of town the battle, if disadvantageous, I have the human to aid you, you do not use the war.”

„OK!”

„”

The heavy iron gate opens slowly, Q-Sword and Jian Feng Han stand up from failure to drop the city wall, summoned mount to come, leading the 200 000 person to go out of town rapidly, many players exited directly to turn the wall to build up outside from the inner city without enough time.

„Thump”

The battle drum sound is thunderous, the distant place, this mystical Giants army has not had any action, in a city wall inside and outside same place rock attack, this has to somewhat confused as before.

Do they actually in want to do?